<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:content='http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/' xmlns:googleplay='http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0' xmlns:itunes='http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd' version='2.0'>

<channel>
        <atom:link href='http://feeds.feedburner.com/all-my-favorite-songs' rel='self' type='application/rss+xml' />
        <title>All My Favorite Songs</title>
        <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com</link>
        <description>Have you ever been curious, as to what music others listen to? All My Favorite Songs is a podcast of uninterrupted music, exclusively curated by others, and dug up from hidden unexpected places.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 12:52:52 +0200</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>&#xA9; 2021 abmc</copyright>
        <ttl>60</ttl>
        <image>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com</link>
                <url>http://antoniocosta.github.io/podcasting/all-my-favorite-songs/all-my-favorite-songs.jpg</url>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs</title>
        </image>
        <itunes:image href='http://antoniocosta.github.io/podcasting/all-my-favorite-songs/all-my-favorite-songs.jpg' />
        <itunes:subtitle>Have you ever been curious, as to what music others listen to? All My Favorite Songs is a podcast of uninterrupted music, exclusively curated by others, and dug up from hidden unexpected places.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Have you ever been curious, as to what music others listen to? All My Favorite Songs is a podcast of uninterrupted music, exclusively curated by others, and dug up from hidden unexpected places.</itunes:summary>        
        <itunes:category text='Music' />
        <itunes:keywords>all, favorite, songs, podcast, music</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:author>abmc</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
                <itunes:name>abmc</itunes:name>
                <itunes:email>abmc@gmx.net</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type>



        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 001 by Weezer - All My Favorite Songs</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com/episode/001</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-001-weezer</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-001-weezer/all-my-favorite-songs-001-weezer.mp3" length="55474791" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <description>Weezer is an American rock band formed in Los Angeles, California, in 1992. Since 2001, the band has consisted of Rivers Cuomo (lead vocals, lead guitar, keyboards), Patrick Wilson (drums, percussion, backing vocals), Brian Bell (guitar, backing vocals, keyboards), and Scott Shriner (bass, backing vocals, keyboards).  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Neil Young, REO Speedwagon, Johnny Cash, Toni Braxton, Yeah Yeah Yeahs, Céline Dion, Sinéad O&#39;Connor</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 14:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 002 by Dinosaur Jr. - 80's Inspirations</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com/episode/002</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-002-dinosaur-jr</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-002-dinosaur-jr/all-my-favorite-songs-002-dinosaur-jr.mp3" length="87193193" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <description>Dinosaur Jr. is an American rock band formed in Amherst, Massachusetts, in 1984, originally simply called Dinosaur until legal issues forced a change in name. The band was founded by J Mascis (guitar, vocals, primary songwriter), Lou Barlow (bass, vocals), and Murph (drums). After three albums on independent labels, the band earned a reputation as one of the formative influences on American alternative rock. Mascis&#39;s drawling vocals and distinct guitar sound, hearkening back to 1960s and 1970s classic rock and characterized by extensive use of feedback and distortion, were highly influential in the alternative rock movement of the 1990s.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Wipers, The Dream Syndicate, True West, The Jesus and Mary Chain, The Birthday Party, Throbbing Gristle, Venom, Accept, Saint Vitus, The Eastern Dark, The Neats, Green On Red, Meat Puppets</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 14:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 003 by Drive Like Jehu - All Tomorrow's Parties 2.0</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com/episode/003</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-003-drive-like-jehu</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-003-drive-like-jehu/all-my-favorite-songs-003-drive-like-jehu.mp3" length="141216629" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <description>Drive Like Jehu was an American post-hardcore band from San Diego active from 1990 to 1995. It was formed by rhythm guitarist and vocalist Rick Froberg and lead guitarist John Reis, ex-members of Pitchfork, along with bassist Mike Kennedy and drummer Mark Trombino, both from Night Soil Man, after their two bands disbanded in 1990. Drive Like Jehu&#39;s music was characterized by passionate singing, unusual song structure, indirect melodic themes, intricate guitar playing, and calculated use of tension, resulting in a distinctive sound amongst other post-hardcore acts and helped to catalyze the evolution of hardcore punk into emo.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode all songs by bands selected by Drive Like Jehu to play All Tomorrow&#39;s Parties 2.0 April 22-24, 2016.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Hot Snakes, The Blind Shake, Mrs. Magician, Flamin&#39; Groovies, The King Khan &amp; BBQ Show, The Schizophonics, Metz, Mission Of Burma, The Gories, King Khan and the Shrines, The Spits, Rocket From The Crypt, Betunizer, The Monkeywrench, Holly Golightly, Dan Sartain, Martin Rev, Tortoise, The Ex, PyPy, Gary Wilson, Claw Hammer, Wau y Los Arrrghs</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 14:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 004 by Viagra Boys - Shrimptech Enterprises Vol.1</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com/episode/004</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-004-viagra-boys</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-004-viagra-boys/all-my-favorite-songs-004-viagra-boys.mp3" length="349118067" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <description>Viagra Boys are a Swedish post-punk band from Stockholm. The band was formed in 2015, with several members coming from the bands Les Big Byrd, Pig Eyes, Nine, Nitad and Neu-Ronz. In 2018, they released their first album, Street Worms. Nils Hansson, a journalist at the newspaper Dagens Nyheter described the band favorably, praising their musical style, as well as their use of black humor and satire, and rated the album a five out of five. In 2019, the band won the Independent Music Companies Association (IMPALA) Album of the Year Award for Street Worms. The band&#39;s second album, Welfare Jazz, was released in January 2021.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: Tubeway Army, The Jesus and Mary Chain, Chain and The Gang, DEVO, Goran Kajfes Subtropic Arkestra, Goran Kajfes, Roxy Music, Built To Spill, The Stooges, Waylon Jennings, Clap Your Hands Say Yeah, DAF, The Stooges, Broadcast, Container, Run The Jewels, Spacemen 3, Daniel Lanois, Anna Domino, Rocket From The Tombs, Esbjörn Svensson Trio, Missing Persons, Pere Ubu, Christian Scott aTunde Adjuah, Elena Pinderhughes, Tom Tom Club, 13th Floor Elevators, Sleaford Mods, John Coltrane, Art Ensemble Of Chicago, Pixies, Fire! Orchestra, Richard Hell, The Breeders, Daniel Ögren, Sam Rivers, Chris &amp; Cosey, The Soft Boys, Hawkwind, Joni Mitchell</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

</channel>

</rss>

