<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:content='http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/' xmlns:googleplay='http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0' xmlns:itunes='http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd' version='2.0'>

<channel>
        <atom:link href='https://feeds.feedburner.com/all-my-favorite-songs' rel='self' type='application/rss+xml' />
        <title>All My Favorite Songs</title>
        <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com</link>
        <description>Have you ever been curious, as to what music others listen to? All My Favorite Songs is a podcast of uninterrupted music, exclusively curated by others, and dug up from hidden unexpected places.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 13:44:04 +0100</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>&#xA9; 2023 A Bee MC</copyright>
        <ttl>60</ttl>
        <image>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com</link>
                <url>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com/img/all-my-favorite-songs.jpg</url>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs</title>
        </image>
        <itunes:image href='https://allmyfavoritesongs.com/img/all-my-favorite-songs.jpg' />
        <itunes:subtitle>Have you ever been curious, as to what music others listen to? All My Favorite Songs is a podcast of uninterrupted music, exclusively curated by others, and dug up from hidden unexpected places.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Have you ever been curious, as to what music others listen to? All My Favorite Songs is a podcast of uninterrupted music, exclusively curated by others, and dug up from hidden unexpected places.</itunes:summary>        
        <itunes:category text='Music' />
        <itunes:keywords>all, favorite, songs, podcast, music</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:author>A Bee MC</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
                <itunes:name>A Bee MC</itunes:name>
                <itunes:email>abmc@gmx.net</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type>



        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 046 by Keanu Reeves - Favorite bands of all time</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#046</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-046-keanu-reeves</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-046-keanu-reeves/all-my-favorite-songs-046-keanu-reeves.mp3" length="281049375" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-046-keanu-reeves/all-my-favorite-songs-046-keanu-reeves.jpg' />
                <description>Keanu Charles Reeves (born September 2, 1964), whose first name means &#39;cool breeze over the mountains&#39; in Hawaiian, is a Canadian actor who found his greatest success in comedy, science-fiction, and action movies. Born in Beirut. Lebanon and raised in Toronto, Canada, Reeves began acting in theatre productions and in television films before making his feature film debut in Youngblood (1986). He had his breakthrough role in the science fiction comedy Bill &amp; Ted&#39;s Excellent Adventure (1989), and he reprised his role in its sequels. He gained praise for playing a hustler in the independent drama My Own Private Idaho (1991) and established himself as an action hero with leading roles in Point Break (1991) and Speed (1994). Greater stardom came for playing Neo in the science fiction series The Matrix, beginning in 1999.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In addition to acting, Reeves has directed the film Man of Tai Chi (2013). He has played bass guitar for the band Dogstar and pursued other endeavours such as writing and philanthropy.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This episode features 5 songs by each of the 10 ands that Reeves named his all-time favorites. Taken from a 1996 interview to Entertainment Weekly, but also from additional subsequent interviews during his Dogstar days two decades later, and up to 2014.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Fugazi, Ramones, The Exploited, Discharge, Elvis Costello, Elvis Costello &amp; The Attractions, The Clash, Violent Femmes, Joy Division, Minor Threat, Bad Brains</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 045 by The Chats - Rage Guest</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#045</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-045-the-chats</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-045-the-chats/all-my-favorite-songs-045-the-chats.mp3" length="315134408" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-045-the-chats/all-my-favorite-songs-045-the-chats.jpg' />
                <description>The Chats are an Australian punk rock band that formed in 2016 in the Sunshine Coast, Queensland. They describe their sound as &#39;shed rock&#39;. The current band lineup is composed of guitarist Josh Hardy, drummer Matt Boggis, and bassist and vocalist Eamon Sandwith. The Chats make rambunctious old-school punk peppered with their cheeky, irreverent sense of humor. More interested in beer, smokes, and fast cars than the state of the world, the Chats follow in the tradition of Australian bands like the Cosmic Psychos, the Hard-Ons, and Dune Rats in cranking out raw, energetic punk with a smirking sense of fun and a regular-guy attitude. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode all songs selected by The Chats as guests for Australian TV show Rage, on September 14 2019.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; The Stooges, Frenzal Rhomb, Tony Dork, BadDreems, Tenacious D, Sex Pistols, LES LULLIES, Boing Boing, The Clash, The Unknowns, Tommy and the Commies, The Cavemen., Cosmic Psychos, Drunk Mums, C.O.F.F.I.N, Flight To Dubai, Pist Idiots, IDLES, The Living Eyes, STORK, WOD, Peter Bibby, Clowns, The Clean, XTC, DEVO, Black Eyed Peas, ACDC, The Angels, Deep Purple, Bob Dylan, Cold Chisel, Midnight Oil, J.J. Cale, Daryl Hall &amp; John Oates, Hello Sailor, The Bats, Mötley Crüe, Def Leppard, The Chats</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 044 by Busy P - On My Stereo</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#044</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-044-busy-p</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-044-busy-p/all-my-favorite-songs-044-busy-p.mp3" length="306207323" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-044-busy-p/all-my-favorite-songs-044-busy-p.jpg' />
                <description>Pedro Winter (born Pierre Winter; 21 April 1975), also known by the stage name Busy P, is a French record producer, DJ, record label owner, and former artist manager. After being the manager of Daft Punk from 1996 to 2008, he founded the electronic music label Ed Banger Records, in which he signed artists like Justice, Breakbot, SebastiAn, Cassius, Mr. Oizo, DJ Mehdi and Myd among others. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode all time favourites as released by Winter as a playlist on a popular music streaming platform (that shall remain unnamed), between May and December 2017.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Vladimir Cauchemar, Myd, Red Axes, Post Malone, 21 Savage, Nosaj Thing, Charlotte Gainsbourg, Siriusmo, Justice, LCD Soundsystem, Arnaud Rebotini, London Grammar, Busy P, Boston Bun, Royal Blood, Soulwax, Feist, Pépite, Parcels, Thundercat, Pharrell Williams, Kendrick Lamar, Madlib, Jeff Mills, Mr Flash, Brodinski, JAY-Z, Kanye West, Lucien Kimono, Tepr, DJ Hell, Corine, Dopplereffekt, Hugues Rey, DJ Mehdi, 10LEC6, Mary J. Blige, KAYTRANADA, BADBADNOTGOOD, Future, Amber Mark, Cashmere Cat</description>
                <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 043 by Kim Gordon - Sit in for Iggy Pop</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#043</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-043-kim-gordon</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-043-kim-gordon/all-my-favorite-songs-043-kim-gordon.mp3" length="228118993" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-043-kim-gordon/all-my-favorite-songs-043-kim-gordon.jpg' />
                <description>Kim Althea Gordon (born April 28, 1953) is an American musician, singer, and songwriter, best known as the bassist, guitarist, and vocalist of alternative rock band Sonic Youth. During her time with that band, her smoky, half-spoken, half-sung vocals and feminist viewpoint added depth to their experimental rock and made her a major figure on the American indie rock scene from the &#39;80s onward. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode the full playlist of songs played by Gordon on April 3rd 2020, when sitting in for Iggy Pop on his BBC Radio 6 show.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; The Fall, Nina Simone, Alice Coltrane, Pharoah Sanders, The Stooges, DNA, J Mascis, Heron Oblivion, Missy Elliott, PJ Harvey, Gold Dime, Television, Talk Normal, Neil Young, Crazy Horse, Brigitte Fontaine, Eleanor Friedberger, Linda Ronstadt, Stina Nordenstam, Aimee Mann, Nas, Nico, Karen Dalton, Mira, Islaja, Mazzy Star, Abbey Lincoln, Cardi B, Charli XCX, Patty Waters</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 042 by Stephen King - Favorite songs of all time</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#042</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-042-stephen-king</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-042-stephen-king/all-my-favorite-songs-042-stephen-king.mp3" length="444787702" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-042-stephen-king/all-my-favorite-songs-042-stephen-king.jpg' />
                <description>Stephen Edwin King (born September 21, 1947) is an American author of horror, supernatural fiction, suspense, crime, science-fiction, and fantasy novels. Described as the &#39;King of Horror&#39;, a play on his surname and a reference to his high standing in pop culture, his books have sold more than 350 million copies, and many have been adapted into films, television series, miniseries, and comic books. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode a list gathered from the many bands and artists Stephen King has professed his love for over the years.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Spoon, Alejandro Escovedo, Slobberbone, James McMurtry, Alan Jackson, The Beach Boys, Chuck Prophet, Henry Mancini, The Inmates, The Raveonettes, Michael McDermott, Ollabelle, Diesel Doug &amp; the Long Haul Truckers, Tim Easton, Billy Bragg, Wilco, Ryan Adams, The Gothic Archies, Rhett Miller, The Beatles, Judas Priest, Ramones, Kenny Wayne Shepherd, Shooter Jennings, Flogging Molly, Ricky Nelson, Al Kooper, Jimmy Vivino, Thelma Houston, KC &amp; The Sunshine Band, LCD Soundsystem, John Mellencamp, ACDC, Danny &amp; The Juniors, Jan &amp; Dean, The Rolling Stones, The Standells, The Kingsmen, Creedence Clearwater Revival, Johnny Rivers, The Searchers, Nathaniel Rateliff &amp; The Night Sweats, The Knack, Iron Butterfly, John Cafferty &amp; the Beaver Brown Band, Chuck Berry, Lyres, The Hollies, Metallica, Anthrax, Pantera, Sex Pistols, Little Richard, The Dominoes And Billie Wand, Elvis Presley, Mickey Hawks, Wanda Jackson, Gary U.S. Bonds, Bruce Springsteen, Eddie Cochran, Connie Francis, Elvis Costello, Rancid, Langhorne Slim, The Tractors, Shawn Mullins, The Rockin&#39; Rebels, Janis Ian, Alvin &#39;Youngblood&#39; Hart &amp; Teenie Hodges, Sam Cooke, Jimmy Buffett, Phil Vassar, Fred Eaglesmith, Tom Rush, Richard Thompson, The Cramps, The Manhattan Transfer, Tift Merritt, Bright Eyes, Mavis Staples</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 041 by Josh Homme - Fill in for Jarvis Cocker</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#041</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-041-josh-homme</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-041-josh-homme/all-my-favorite-songs-041-josh-homme.mp3" length="197710596" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-041-josh-homme/all-my-favorite-songs-041-josh-homme.jpg' />
                <description>Joshua Michael Homme (born May 17, 1973) is an American musician, singer, and songwriter. Homme has been part of two of the most acclaimed stoner rock/metal bands of the late &#39;90s and early 2000s, Kyuss and Queens of the Stone Age. He is best known as the founder, primary songwriter, and only continuous member of the rock band Queens of the Stone Age, which he formed in 1996 and in which he sings lead vocals and plays guitar, as well as occasionally playing bass and drums. He also co-founded Eagles of Death Metal in 1998, playing drums and bass for their studio recordings and occasionally performing live with them. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode the full collection of songs played by Homme on Jan 2nd 2014, when filling in for Jarvis Cocker on his BBC Radio 6 radio show called Sunday Service (aired from 2010 to 2017). An eclectic two-hour mix of music from Homme&#39;s record collection, with a definite nod towards the darkside and the downright dirty.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Screamin&#39; Jay Hawkins, WhoMadeWho, The Cramps, The Damned, Björk, Primal Scream, The Saints, The Doors, Iceage, Bill Withers, Bauhaus, Roky Erickson, Sly &amp; The Family Stone, Savages, Komeda, Misfits, Glenn Danzig, Gnonnas Pedro et ses Dadjes, Eagles Of Death Metal, Grimes, Beck, Blonde Redhead, Cat Power, Ramones, ACDC, Iggy Pop, Arctic Monkeys, Bobby &#39;Boris&#39; Pickett</description>
                <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 040 by Anthony Bourdain - 25 Favorite Songs To Cook To</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#040</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-040-anthony-bourdain</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-040-anthony-bourdain/all-my-favorite-songs-040-anthony-bourdain.mp3" length="201007156" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-040-anthony-bourdain/all-my-favorite-songs-040-anthony-bourdain.jpg' />
                <description>Anthony Michael Bourdain (June 25, 1956 – June 8, 2018) was an American celebrity chef, author, and travel documentarian who starred in programs focusing on the exploration of international culture, cuisine, and the human condition. Bourdain was a figure who became synonymous with non-conformity and a determination to forge his own path, regardless of the hurdles in front of him. Whether through his progressive food, his dedication to the dive bar and all its inhabitants, or his adoration of all things punk, Anthony Bourdain was a bastion of anti-establishment splendour and he was determined to integrate his two passions. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode the list of perfect songs to cook to, created by Bourdain for his PBS show The Mind of a Chef, that aired in 6 seasons from 2012 to 2017.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Bobby Womack, Curtis Mayfield, Mark Lanegan, Bill Withers, Bob Dylan, Roxy Music, Bush Tetras, Johnny Thunders, The Chambers Brothers, Pretenders, The Velvet Underground, A Tribe Called Quest, Tony! Toni! Toné!, The Brian Jonestown Massacre, Stevie Ray Vaughan, Sly &amp; The Family Stone, Ryuichi Sakamoto, The Rolling Stones, Randy Crawford, Porno for Pyros, Jacques Dutronc, Ennio Morricone, John Barry, Elvis Costello &amp; The Attractions, Earth, Wind &amp; Fire</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 039 by Lou Reed - What I'm Listening To</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#039</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-039-lou-reed</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-039-lou-reed/all-my-favorite-songs-039-lou-reed.mp3" length="166863481" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-039-lou-reed/all-my-favorite-songs-039-lou-reed.jpg' />
                <description>Lewis Allan Reed (March 2, 1942 - October 27, 2013) was an American musician, singer, songwriter, and poet. He was the guitarist, singer, and principal songwriter for the rock band the Velvet Underground and had a solo career that spanned five decades. Although not commercially successful during its existence, the Velvet Underground became regarded as one of the most influential bands in the history of underground and alternative rock music. Reed&#39;s distinctive deadpan voice, poetic and transgressive lyrics, and experimental guitar playing were trademarks throughout his long career. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode a compilation of Reed&#39;s final two playlists curated by himself (for a popular online music streaming platform that shall remain unnamed), before he passed in 2013, revealing what he was listening to in his final days.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Nicki Minaj, Albert Ayler, Roy Orbison, Prince, Fucked Up, The King Khan &amp; BBQ Show, Waylon Jennings, Georgia Anne Muldrow, Captain Beefheart &amp; His Magic Band, of Montreal, Ricky Nelson, Tom Waits, Miles Davis, Deerhoof, Antony and the Johnsons, Howlin&#39; Wolf, Lonnie Johnson, Otis Redding, Emily Haines &amp; The Soft Skeleton, Perfume Genius, Ty Segall, Leonard Cohen, Dr. Dog, Napalm Death, Eddy Current Suppression Ring, Daughter, Robyn</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 038 by Lou Reed - 100 Favorite Songs Of All Time</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#038</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-038-lou-reed</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-038-lou-reed/all-my-favorite-songs-038-lou-reed.mp3" length="475894732" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-038-lou-reed/all-my-favorite-songs-038-lou-reed.jpg' />
                <description>Lewis Allan Reed (March 2, 1942 - October 27, 2013) was an American musician, singer, songwriter, and poet. He was the guitarist, singer, and principal songwriter for the rock band the Velvet Underground and had a solo career that spanned five decades. Although not commercially successful during its existence, the Velvet Underground became regarded as one of the most influential bands in the history of underground and alternative rock music. Reed&#39;s distinctive deadpan voice, poetic and transgressive lyrics, and experimental guitar playing were trademarks throughout his long career. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode 100 of the songs Reed considered the greatest of all time, as shared with the Helsinki Music Club in 2004.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Ornette Coleman, Eddie &amp; Ernie, Rahsaan Roland Kirk, Ray Charles, Little Richard, The Excellents, Lorraine Ellison, Elvis Presley, Carl Perkins, Chuck Berry, Billy Lee Riley, Wanda Jackson, Nolan Strong &amp; The Diablos, Roy Orbison, Musical Creations Studio Musicians (Karaoke), Fats Domino, Dion &amp; The Belmonts, Hank Williams, Bo Diddley, Chris Connor, Chet Baker, Jimmy Scott, The Mellows, Otis Redding, Jimi Hendrix, Ike &amp; Tina Turner, Sam Cooke, Jerry Lee Lewis, J.J. Cale, Ry Cooder, (question mark) &amp; The Mysterians, Ameritz Top Tracks, Huey &#39;Piano&#39; Smith, His Clowns, Bobby Charles, Clarence &#39;Frogman&#39; Henry, Jimmy Reed, John Lee Hooker, Albert King, Booker T. &amp; the M.G.&#39;s, Wilson Pickett, Sam &amp; Dave, The Youngbloods, The Left Banke, The Students, Jackie &amp; The Starlites, The Easybeats, The Cadillacs, Hank Ballard &amp; The Midnighters, B.B. King, Al Green, Ricky Nelson, James Brown &amp; The Famous Flames, Laurie Anderson, Kate Bush, The Beach Boys, Link Wray, Ann Peebles, Skeeter Davis, Bob Dylan, Peter Gabriel, Carpenters, Charlie Dore, The Rolling Stones, Bobby &#39;Blue&#39; Bland, Solomon Burke, Sly &amp; The Family Stone, Etta James, Carla Thomas, Clarence Carter, Aretha Franklin, Ameritz Karaoke Entertainment, James &amp; Bobby Purify, Aaron Neville, Lee Dorsey, Detroit, U2, John Lennon, Moe Tucker, Stevie Wonder, Marvin Gaye, The Chiffons</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 037 by Robert Smith - Top 30 Favorite Songs From The 80s</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#037</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-037-robert-smith</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-037-robert-smith/all-my-favorite-songs-037-robert-smith.mp3" length="229078401" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-037-robert-smith/all-my-favorite-songs-037-robert-smith.jpg' />
                <description>Robert James Smith (born 21 April 1959) is an English singer, songwriter, musician, and record producer. He is best known as the lead singer, guitarist, primary songwriter, and only continuous member of the rock band the Cure, which he co-founded in 1978. He was also the lead guitarist for the band Siouxsie and the Banshees from 1982 to 1984, and was part of the short-lived group the Glove in 1983. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Smith is known for his guitar-playing style, distinctive voice, and fashion sense, with the latter—a pale complexion, smeared red lipstick, black eye-liner, a dishevelled nest of wiry black hair, and all-black clothes—being highly influential on the goth subculture that rose to prominence in the 1980s. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Cure in 2019. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode Smith&#39;s top 30 favorite songs of the 1980s (in alphabetical order) as selected by himself for a special two-hour show he hosted on Sirius XM’s 1st Wave channel on May 24, 2009.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; ABC, The Associates, Fun Boy Three, Bananarama, David Bowie, Kate Bush, Cocteau Twins, Cristina, DAF, Depeche Mode, Dinosaur Jr., Echo &amp; the Bunnymen, Peter Gabriel, The Human League, The Jesus and Mary Chain, Joy Division, Chaka Khan, Madness, Mel &amp; Kim, my bloody valentine, New Order, Yoko Ono, Danny Tenaglia, Pixies, Pretenders, Prince, The Psychedelic Furs, Siouxsie and the Banshees, Soft Cell, The Sugarcubes, Suzanne Vega, Tom Waits</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 036 by Frank Zappa - Fraudulent DJ (part 2 of 2)</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#036</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-036-frank-zappa</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-036-frank-zappa/all-my-favorite-songs-036-frank-zappa.mp3" length="504840537" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-036-frank-zappa/all-my-favorite-songs-036-frank-zappa.jpg' />
                <description>Frank Vincent Zappa (December 21, 1940 – December 4, 1993) was an American musician, singer, composer, songwriter and bandleader. His work is characterized by nonconformity, free-form improvisation, sound experiments, musical virtuosity and satire of American culture. In a career spanning more than 30 years, Zappa composed rock, pop, jazz, jazz fusion, orchestral and musique concrète works, and produced almost all of the 60-plus albums that he released with his band the Mothers of Invention and as a solo artist. Zappa also directed feature-length films and music videos, and designed album covers. He is considered one of the most innovative and stylistically diverse musicians of his generation. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On a number of occasions Zappa appeared in radio show slots, airing and generally discussing his favored music, or occasionally guesting on a &#39;club turntable&#39;, describing himself as a &#39;Fraudulent DJ&#39;. In this episode, part two of a series of two, all the tracks in chronological order as selected by Zappa (with exception of most of his own tracks) for all his DJ appearances that have been documented, and that took place between 1968 and 1984.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Frank Zappa, Jimi Hendrix, Alice Cooper, Led Zeppelin, The Clovers, The Lamplighters, The Mothers Of Invention, Captain Beefheart &amp; His Magic Band, Igor Stravinsky, Columbia Symphony Orchestra, John Lee Hooker, The Rolling Stones, The Young Rascals, Howlin&#39; Wolf, The Velours, The Channels, Earl Lewis, Joni Mitchell, Muddy Waters, Jimmy Reed, Blondie, The Specials, Gerry &amp; The Holograms, Nina Hagen, The Jets, Konrad Koselleck Big Band, Ellen Ten Damme, U.K. Subs, Snuky Tate, Robert &amp; Johnny, The Flying Lizards, Joe Jackson, Gary Numan, The Police, Destroy All Monsters, The Saints, L Shankar, The Tubes, Suburban Lawns, Captain Beefheart, John Cooper Clarke, Public Image Ltd., The Firemen, The Deadliners, Plastics, Jeff Simmons, New Musik, Edgard Varèse, Polish National Radio Symphony Orchestra, Christopher Lyndon-Gee, ZZ Top, The Velvet Underground, Nico, Black Sabbath, Lene Lovich, The GTOs, Queen, Lynyrd Skynyrd, The Top Charts D.J., The Beatles, SpizzEnergi, Traffic, Wild Man Fischer, Lew Lewis, Tomorrow, Frankie Valli, Blue Öyster Cult, Foreigner, ACDC, Sue Saad &amp; the Next, Van Halen, Buzzcocks, The Jam, Pink Floyd, Journey</description>
                <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 035 by Frank Zappa - Fraudulent DJ (part 1 of 2)</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#035</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-035-frank-zappa</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-035-frank-zappa/all-my-favorite-songs-035-frank-zappa.mp3" length="365289324" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-035-frank-zappa/all-my-favorite-songs-035-frank-zappa.jpg' />
                <description>Frank Vincent Zappa (December 21, 1940 – December 4, 1993) was an American musician, singer, composer, songwriter and bandleader. His work is characterized by nonconformity, free-form improvisation, sound experiments, musical virtuosity and satire of American culture. In a career spanning more than 30 years, Zappa composed rock, pop, jazz, jazz fusion, orchestral and musique concrète works, and produced almost all of the 60-plus albums that he released with his band the Mothers of Invention and as a solo artist. Zappa also directed feature-length films and music videos, and designed album covers. He is considered one of the most innovative and stylistically diverse musicians of his generation. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On a number of occasions Zappa appeared in radio show slots, airing and generally discussing his favored music, or occasionally guesting on a &#39;club turntable&#39;, describing himself as a &#39;Fraudulent DJ&#39;. In this episode, part one of a series of two, all the tracks in chronological order as selected by Zappa (with exception of most of his own tracks) for all his DJ appearances that have been documented, and that took place between 1968 and 1984.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Frank Zappa, The Mothers Of Invention, Ewan MacColl, The Hollywood Persuaders, Pierre Boulez, Hilary Summers, Ensemble Intercontemporain, The Dreamlovers, The Penguins, Charles Mingus, Frankie Lee Sims, Vernon Green &amp; The Medallions, Richard Berry &amp; The Dreamers, The Paragons, Big Moose, The Turbans, Johnny Guitar Watson, The Spaniels, J.B. Lenoir, Vernon Green, The Medallions, Bill Haley &amp; His Comets, The Chips, The Velvets, Richard Berry &amp; The Pharaohs, Johnny &#39;Guitar&#39; Watson, The Feathers, Don &amp; Dewey, The Jewels, The Cufflinks, Johnny Ace, Wilbur Whitfield &amp; The Pleasers, Hank Ballard &amp; The Midnighters, Jackie &amp; The Starlites, The Cellos, The Rolling Crew, Screamin&#39; Jay Hawkins, Paul Robeson, Huey &#39;Piano&#39; Smith, Clarence &#39;Gatemouth&#39; Brown, The Six Teens, The Laurie Sisters, Lloyd Terrell, Ruben And The Jets, The Hawks, The Olympics, Andre Williams, The Gaylarks, Little Sunny Day and the Clouds, The Clovers, The Harptones, Baby Ray And The Ferns, Muddy Waters, The Shaggs, Richard Berry, The Robins, Bob Landers, Willie Joe, Tony Allen, Peppermint Harris, The El Dorados, The 5 Campbells, Elmore James, The Moonlighters, Don Julian, The Larks, Lloyd Price, The Solitaires, Black Oak Arkansas, Edgard Varèse, Frederic Waldman, NY Wind Ensemble, Olivier Messiaen, BBC Symphony OrchestraAntal Dorati, Antal Doráti, BBC Symphony Orchestra, Anton Webern, Nürnberg Symphony Orchestra, Othmar Maga</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 034 by Peaches - Wise Women Playlist</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#034</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-034-peaches</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-034-peaches/all-my-favorite-songs-034-peaches.mp3" length="192077425" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-034-peaches/all-my-favorite-songs-034-peaches.jpg' />
                <description>Merrill Nisker (born 11 November 1966), better known by her stage name Peaches, is a Canadian electroclash musician and producer who burst into transcontinental favor with her very particular brand of cocksure rapping and groovebox beats. Peaches was an unlikely success story, making her musical mark after the age of 30 in a genre not commonly known for recognizing its female or its aging participants. Her unique rapping style and stage show brought her great popularity first in Europe and then in North America. Some of her lyrics and performances have been rejected due to them being potentially offensive, and a lot of her songs are themed on gender identity. Her work propagates sexual freedom and reversal of gender roles. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode Peaches selecting some of her favourite music for her Wise Women BBC Radio 6 Music takeover on December 2015.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; A Taste Of Honey, Björk, David Bowie, Missy Elliott, PJ Harvey, L7, L&#39;Trimm, Krisma, Suicide, Light Asylum, Laurie Anderson, Kate Bush, Planningtorock, Roberta Flack, M.I.A., Nire, Maluca, Nani Castle, Lafawndah, Kim Carnes, Savages, Lizzy Mercier Descloux, Sinéad O&#39;Connor, Yma Sumac, Diamanda Galás, The Regrettes, TT The Artist, Althea And Donna</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 033 by Iggy Pop - Most Influential Songs &amp; Favorite Albums</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#033</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-033-iggy-pop</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-033-iggy-pop/all-my-favorite-songs-033-iggy-pop.mp3" length="110585851" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-033-iggy-pop/all-my-favorite-songs-033-iggy-pop.jpg' />
                <description>James Newell Osterberg Jr. (born April 21, 1947), known professionally as Iggy Pop, is an American musician, singer, and songwriter. Designated the &#39;Godfather of Punk&#39;, he was the vocalist and lyricist of proto-punk band The Stooges, who were formed in 1967 and have disbanded and reunited many times since. Years before punk musicians became known for antagonistic on-stage behavior, Pop mastered an unhinged approach to performance that sometimes endangered himself and spectators alike. Pop&#39;s music has encompassed a number of styles over the course of his career, including garage rock, punk rock, hard rock, heavy metal, art rock, new wave, jazz, blues, and electronic. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This episode features Pop&#39;s 5 most influential songs, as shared with ABC&#39;s Nightline in 2010, as well as one track from each of Pop&#39;s 12 favorite albums of all time, as shared with Far Out magazine in 2021.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Frank Sinatra, The Ronettes, The Shangri-Las, Muddy Waters with Orchestra, Link Wray, Bob Dylan, The Rolling Stones, David Bowie, Traffic, Marty Robbins, James Brown &amp; The Famous Flames, Jimi Hendrix, The Beatles, John Coltrane, Louis Armstrong &amp; His Hot Five, R.L. Burnside</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 032 by Quentin Tarantino - Film &amp; TV Favorites</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#032</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-032-quentin-tarantino</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-032-quentin-tarantino/all-my-favorite-songs-032-quentin-tarantino.mp3" length="375875405" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-032-quentin-tarantino/all-my-favorite-songs-032-quentin-tarantino.jpg' />
                <description>Quentin Jerome Tarantino (born March 27, 1963) is an American filmmaker, actor, film critic and author. His films are characterized by frequent references to popular culture and film history, nonlinear storylines, dark humor, stylized violence, extended dialogue, pervasive use of profanity, cameos and ensemble casts. Tarantino is also known for his choice of music in his films, including soundtracks that often use songs from the 1960s and 70s.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This episode features 70 tracks curated by Tarantino and that he has used within his work. It was originally published as a playlist with a popular audio streaming provider (that shall remain unnamed) in July 2019.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Nancy Sinatra, Harry Nilsson, Isaac Hayes, Luis Bacalov, Rocky Roberts, Edda Dell&#39;Orso, Dusty Springfield, Jennifer Jason Leigh, Kurt Russell, Samuel L. Jackson, Chuck Berry, Bernard Herrmann, Randy Crawford, The Tornadoes, Santa Esmeralda, T. Rex, Al Hirt, Charlie Feathers, Chris Isaak, The Statler Brothers, David Hess, The Delfonics, The Mavericks, Peggy Simms, George Baker Selection, Joe Tex, Soundgarden, Jerome Patrick Hoban, Johnny Cash, Ennio Morricone, Dave Dee, Dozy, Beaky, Mick &amp; Tich, The Lively Ones, Buddy Guy, HOTEI, ZZ Top, Dick Dale, Al Green, The Brothers Johnson, Meiko Kaji, Kim Circle, Malcolm McLaren, Roy Orbison, Alex Orbison, Chuck Turner, Elisa Toffoli, Ricky Nelson, Shivaree, The Soundtrack Singers, Ann O&#39;Day, David Bowie, Smith, The Robins, Jim Croce, The Marketts, The White Stripes, Bill Withers, The Blasters, James Russo, The 5.6.7.8&#39;s, James Brown, 2Pac, Stealers Wheel, Lole Y Manuel, Bloodstone, Brother Dege, Nymphomania, Bobby Womack, Léo Delibes, Kool &amp; The Gang, Robert Palmer, Pacific Gas &amp; Electric</description>
                <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 031 by The Mars Volta - Rage Guest</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#031</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-031-mars-volta</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-031-mars-volta/all-my-favorite-songs-031-mars-volta.mp3" length="265413484" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-031-mars-volta/all-my-favorite-songs-031-mars-volta.jpg' />
                <description>The Mars Volta is an American progressive rock band from El Paso, Texas, formed in 2001. The band&#39;s final live lineup consisted of Omar Rodríguez-López (guitar, producer, direction), Cedric Bixler-Zavala (vocals, lyrics), Juan Alderete (bass), Marcel Rodríguez-López (keyboards, percussion), and Deantoni Parks (drums). The band formed following the break-up of Rodríguez-López and Bixler-Zavala&#39;s previous band, At the Drive-In. They are known for their energetic live shows and their concept albums.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode, all songs selected by The Mars Volta as guests for Australian TV show Rage, on August 23 2008 (and reaired on April 3 2021).  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Sonic Youth, Butthole Surfers, The Black Crowes, The Go-Betweens, The Jesus and Mary Chain, Carpenters, Tom Waits, Cliff Richard &amp; The Shadows, Glen Campbell, Thomas Dolby, Gary Numan, Kate Bush, Ciccone Youth, Animal Collective, Dungen, Sweet, Cheap Trick, Suicidal Tendencies, Hüsker Dü, Frank Black, Galaxie 500, Primal Scream, Grinderman, Siouxsie and the Banshees, The Fall, Eric B. &amp; Rakim, Tin Machine, Black Sabbath, Jimi Hendrix, Public Image Ltd., High On Fire, Einstürzende Neubauten, At the Drive-In</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 030 by Lux Interior - The Purple Knif Show</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#030</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-030-lux-interior</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-030-lux-interior/all-my-favorite-songs-030-lux-interior.mp3" length="115940947" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-030-lux-interior/all-my-favorite-songs-030-lux-interior.jpg' />
                <description>Erick Lee Purkhiser (October 21, 1946 – February 4, 2009), better known by the stage name Lux Interior, was an American singer and a founding member of the American band The Cramps - exponents of trash culture and &#39;psychobilly&#39; music - from 1972 until his death in 2009 at age 62.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode Lux Interior&#39;s favorite and obscure 7 inch records, as played by himself in a much sought-after, classic Hollywood radio show he hosted in July of 1984.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; One Way Streets, Bob Hocko, Swamprats, June Jackson, The Trashmen, Link Wray, Bill Carter And The Rovin&#39; Gamblers, The Tides, Earl Hagan &amp; The Interns, Mad Mike And The Maniacs, Billy Strange, Ted Weems &amp; His Orchestra, Ray Anthony &amp; His Orchestra, Gradie O&#39;Neal, The Enchanters, Sam Space, The Cadettes, Archie Bleyer, Vic Mizzy, The Spark Plugs, The Frantics, The Five Blobs, The Troggs, Ward Darby And The Raves, Cozy Cole, The Deadly Ones</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 029 by Sleater Kinney - Selects</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#029</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-029-sleater-kinney</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-029-sleater-kinney/all-my-favorite-songs-029-sleater-kinney.mp3" length="198711075" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-029-sleater-kinney/all-my-favorite-songs-029-sleater-kinney.jpg' />
                <description>Sleater-Kinney is an American rock band that formed in Olympia, Washington, in 1994. The band&#39;s current lineup features Corin Tucker (vocals and guitar) and Carrie Brownstein (guitar and vocals), following the departure of longtime member Janet Weiss (vocals, drums, and harmonica) in 2019. Sleater-Kinney originated as part of the riot grrrl movement and has become a key part of the American indie rock scene. The band is also known for its feminist and left-leaning politics.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode, all songs selected by Sleater Kinney and published as a playlist with a popular audio streaming provider (that shall remain unnamed), on May 11, 2021.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Sleater-Kinney, Bruce Springsteen, Genesis, Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers, Patti Smith, Pretenders, Rufus, Chaka Khan, Glen Campbell, Joni Mitchell, Heart, Grateful Dead, Stevie Wonder, The Band, Jackson Browne, Emmylou Harris, Lucinda Williams, Wilco, The Equals, Joan Armatrading, Fleetwood Mac, Prince, Big Joanie, Talking Heads, Rosanne Cash, Thin Lizzy</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 028 by METZ - Nuggetz (part 2 of 2)</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#028</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-028-metz</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-028-metz/all-my-favorite-songs-028-metz.mp3" length="350976538" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-028-metz/all-my-favorite-songs-028-metz.jpg' />
                <description>METZ is a Canadian noise punk band formed in 2008 in Ottawa and currently based in Toronto. The band consists of guitarist and vocalist Alex Edkins, bassist Chris Slorach and drummer Hayden Menzies. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode, part two of a series of two, all songs selected by METZ and published as a playlist with a popular audio streaming provider (that shall remain unnamed), between Oct 2017 and Aug 2021.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Captain Beefheart &amp; His Magic Band, Porter Wagoner, Josef K, XBXRX, Hoover, Les Savy Fav, Institute, Liars, Mekons, Wrangler Brutes, Head Wound City, A Place To Bury Strangers, U.S. Maple, Oneida, Metz, Freak Heat Waves, Mimico, Pere Ubu, Suicide, The Gories, Public Image Ltd., Cherubs, Plasmalab, Cindy Lee, Tales Of Terror, New Fries, Career Suicide, Wire, The Monorchid, Women, Mission Of Burma, Holy Fuck, Playthings, Wipers, Brian Eno, Tall Dwarfs, Uniform, Angel Olsen, Beak, Brainiac, Grouper, Unwound, Sic Alps, Swell Maps, MX-80, Television Personalities, Six Finger Satellite, Flesh World, Hot Snakes, Chad VanGaalen, Horse Lords, Spray Paint, Sparklehorse, Suburban Lawns, Protomartyr, SUUNS, Raspberry Bulbs, The Cleaners From Venus, Mudhoney, Neil Young, The Dream Syndicate, Elevator To Hell, Converge, Guided By Voices, Bitch Magnet, Lungfish</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 027 by METZ - Nuggetz (part 1 of 2)</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#027</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-027-metz</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-027-metz/all-my-favorite-songs-027-metz.mp3" length="341188074" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-027-metz/all-my-favorite-songs-027-metz.jpg' />
                <description>METZ is a Canadian noise punk band formed in 2008 in Ottawa and currently based in Toronto. The band consists of guitarist and vocalist Alex Edkins, bassist Chris Slorach and drummer Hayden Menzies. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode, part one of a series of two, all songs selected by METZ and published as a playlist with a popular audio streaming provider (that shall remain unnamed), between Oct 2017 and Aug 2021.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Simply Saucer, Hawkwind, Void, Fela Kuti, The Fall, CAN, Sam Cooke, Portishead, Neil Young, MC5, The Stooges, Nick Cave &amp; The Bad Seeds, Ramones, Donny Hathaway, Bob Dylan, Aretha Franklin, Sly &amp; The Family Stone, Earth, Wind &amp; Fire, Soul Glo, Daniel Romano, Joe Wong, FACS, Adulkt Life, Special Interest, Cold Meat, Dog Day, Nape Neck, Sweeping Promises, Wax Chattels, 3Ds, Jesu, Nels Cline, Napalm Death, Crack Cloud, The Pretty Things, Protomartyr, The Flaming Lips, The Monks, Suicide, Pink Floyd, Elevator To Hell, Purple Mountains, IDLES, Mount Eerie, Polvo, Wire, Sebadoh, Palace Music, Bedhead, The Sound, Vector Seven, Spray Paint, Martin Rev, Echo &amp; the Bunnymen, Silver Apples, Swell Maps, Bikini Kill</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 026 by Jeffrey Lee Pierce - Ballads, Train Songs, Rural South and Delta Blues</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#026</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-026-jeffrey-lee-pierce</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-026-jeffrey-lee-pierce/all-my-favorite-songs-026-jeffrey-lee-pierce.mp3" length="114725884" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-026-jeffrey-lee-pierce/all-my-favorite-songs-026-jeffrey-lee-pierce.jpg' />
                <description>Jeffrey Lee Pierce (June 27, 1958 – March 31, 1996) was an American singer, songwriter, guitarist, and author, best remembered as the hard-living guitarist/singer frontman and one of the founding members of The Gun Club, a band that fused the fury of punk with the melodic structures and lyrical obsessions of the blues, creating their own brand of swampy, ramshackle, psychotic, blues- influenced music. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This episode is a re-creation of a 1980 mixtape made by Jeffrey for Brad Dunning, the original drummer of The Gun Club.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Marvin Rainwater, Buck Griffin, Lonesome Lee, Mack Self, Marty Robbins, Johnny Cash, Hank Williams, Drifting Cowboys, Leo Kottke, The Rolling Stones, Big Bill Broonzy, Waylon Jennings, Bob Dylan, Johnny Horton, Conway Twitty, The Count Bishops, Slim Rhodes, Howlin&#39; Wolf</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 025 by Uhh Yeah Dude - Intros &amp; Outros 2021 (part 2 of 2)</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#025</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-025-uhh-yeah-dude</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-025-uhh-yeah-dude/all-my-favorite-songs-025-uhh-yeah-dude.mp3" length="409497397" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-025-uhh-yeah-dude/all-my-favorite-songs-025-uhh-yeah-dude.jpg' />
                <description> Uhh Yeah Dude is a comedy podcast hosted by Seth Romatelli (born September 20, 1973) and Jonathan Larroquette (born August 7, 1977). Episodes have generally aired once a week since 2006, and run about an hour long. The podcast is described as &#39;A weekly roundup of America through the eyes of two American-Americans&#39;.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode, part two of a series of two, all intro and outro songs from the 2021 episodes (#867 to #898) of Uhh Yeah Dude.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Con Funk Shun, Leo Kottke, The KLF, Ted Greene, Felbm, Holger Czukay, J4soul Musique, Gina X Performance, Joseph Spence, Erkin Koray, Barış Manço, Soft Machine, Grateful Dead, NEU!, Max Romeo, The Upsetters, Prince Jazzbo, Les Sins, Ariel Kalma, SFV Acid, Touché, Yomano, Moodymann, Curved Light, The Horn, Gwen Guthrie, Moderna, Theus Mago, Charlie Haden Quartet West, Cienfuegos, El Gran Combo De Puerto Rico, Andy Montañez, King Sunny AdŽ, Azymuth, Lijadu Sisters, Bill Frisell, Imagination, Pat Martino, Three 6 Mafia, Maxo Kream, Black Brothers, The Outlaw Blues Band, Gábor Szabó, João Gilberto, Frijid Pink, Patrick Cowley, The Beginning Of The End, Sonny Clark, Jim Hall, Ron Carter, Instrumental Group Cabas, WAHM (FR)</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 024 by Uhh Yeah Dude - Intros &amp; Outros 2021 (part 1 of 2)</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#024</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-024-uhh-yeah-dude</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-024-uhh-yeah-dude/all-my-favorite-songs-024-uhh-yeah-dude.mp3" length="411772307" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-024-uhh-yeah-dude/all-my-favorite-songs-024-uhh-yeah-dude.jpg' />
                <description>Uhh Yeah Dude is a comedy podcast hosted by Seth Romatelli (born September 20, 1973) and Jonathan Larroquette (born August 7, 1977). Episodes have generally aired once a week since 2006, and run about an hour long. The podcast is described as &#39;A weekly roundup of America through the eyes of two American-Americans&#39;.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode, part one of a series of two, all intro and outro songs from the 2021 episodes (#838 to #866) of Uhh Yeah Dude.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Neil Young, Tuxedomoon, Squarepusher, Norma Tanega, Captain Torkive, I-Robots, Steve Hillage, Sonya Spence, CAN, Michael Nesmith, The First National Band, PRISM, Susumu Yokota, Dorothy Ashby, Sonny Sharrock Band, Kuruki, Bill Laswell, Dan Curtin, Patrick Cowley, Sylvester, Eddie Hazel, COMPLEX, Dub Specialist, DJ Re Edit, Lena Platonos, Brian Bennett, Bonobo, Capitol K, Paul Blackford, Cerrone, Abba Gargando, John Beltran, CN, Bill Orcutt, Eddie Murphy, Buddy Emmons, Richenel, Bucky Barrett, Ashra, Dog Soldier, Terekke, Delaney &amp; Bonnie, Davey Graham, The Action, Rodney Crowell, Hank Williams, Drifting Cowboys, Black Uhuru, Ahmad Jamal Trio, Intrusion, Rick Barranco, Grateful Dead, Takako Minekawa, Culture, Bohannon, Con Funk Shun, The Bar-Kays, Yarbrough &amp; Peoples, Audience, Indian Ocean</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 023 by The Hives - New Year's Eve</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#023</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-023-the-hives</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-023-the-hives/all-my-favorite-songs-023-the-hives.mp3" length="265078454" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-023-the-hives/all-my-favorite-songs-023-the-hives.jpg' />
                <description>The Hives are a Swedish rock band that rose to prominence in the early 2000s during the Garage Rock Revival. Eight years into their career, the Hives rose from garage rock stalwarts to one of the trendiest bands of the early 2000s, along with the Strokes and the White Stripes. Mixing arty contrivances such as a strict black-and-white dress code and the guidance of a (possibly imaginary) Svengali named Randy Fitzsimmons with Stooges-inspired rock, the Hives - Nicholaus Arson, Chris Dangerous, Dr. Matt Destruction, Vigilante Carlstroem, and Howlin&#39; Pelle Almqvist - formed in 1993 in Fagersta, Sweden, while they were still in their teens.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode the playlist published by the band for New Year&#39;s Eve 2020-21.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; ABBA, Viagra Boys, Amy Taylor, Los Saicos, The Cramps, ShitKid, Jacqueline Taieb, Hunx &amp; His Punx, First Aid Kit, Tom Waits, Shannon &amp; The Clams, Radioactivity, Turbonegro, The Hives, Oblivians, New Bomb Turks, The Sonics, Thee Headcoatees, Reigning Sound, Richard Hell, Sonic&#39;s Rendezvous Band, The Hellacopters, Dead Kennedys, Ramones, Electric Eels, Bo Diddley, Mohammed Wardi, King Gizzard &amp; The Lizard Wizard, Charlie Megira, Julian Casablancas, Franska Trion, Tonbruket, The Wailers, Clinic, Mattiel, The Mysterians, The Stooges</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 022 by Brian Eno - 13 Favorite Albums and Tracks</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#022</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-022-brian-eno</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-022-brian-eno/all-my-favorite-songs-022-brian-eno.mp3" length="145769058" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-022-brian-eno/all-my-favorite-songs-022-brian-eno.jpg' />
                <description>Brian Peter George St John le Baptiste de la Salle Eno (born Brian Peter George Eno, 15 May 1948) is a British musician, composer, record producer and visual artist best known for his pioneering work in ambient music and contributions to rock, pop and electronica. A self-described &#39;non-musician&#39;, Eno has helped introduce unique conceptual approaches and recording techniques to contemporary music. He has been described as one of popular music&#39;s most influential and innovative figures.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode some of Eno&#39;s favorite records and tracks, as shared with William Doyle and published by The Quietus magazine on April 13, 2016.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Maceo Woods, The Christian Tabernacle Concert Choir, Farid al-Atrash, Arif Sağ, Belkıs Akkale, Sabahat Akkiraz, Nuray Hafiftas, The Golden Gate Quartet, Sly &amp; The Family Stone, Meshell Ndegeocello, The Velvet Underground, Steve Reich, Fela Kuti, my bloody valentine, Owen Pallett, Svetoslav Obretenov Bulgarian Choir, Joni Mitchell</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 021 by Marcelo D2 - Atitude Black Punk</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#021</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-021-marcelo-d2</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-021-marcelo-d2/all-my-favorite-songs-021-marcelo-d2.mp3" length="197215597" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-021-marcelo-d2/all-my-favorite-songs-021-marcelo-d2.jpg' />
                <description>Marcelo Maldonado Peixoto (born November 5, 1967), also known as Marcelo D2, is a Brazilian rapper and singer from Rio de Janeiro, Brazil. Acclaimed by young people, he is known for his unique style of rapping, which blends in the traditional Brazilian samba. Living in the poor suburbs, he grew up between the &#39;favelas&#39; and the streets of Andarai, far from postcard Rio and its rich seaside districts.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode a playlist created and published by D2 between May 2017 and Nov 2020.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Death, X-Ray Spex, The Selecter, ESG, Glorious Din, Colourbox, A.R. Kane, Pure Hell, Basement 5, Ho99o9, Bad Brains, KennyHoopla, Tyler, The Creator, Hodgy, Earl Sweatshirt, Antwon, Flatbush Zombies, Vince Staples, Big Joanie, The OBGMs, TCIYF, Red Arkade, Madvillain</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 020 by Run The Jewels - Rage Guest (part 2 of 2)</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#020</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-020-run-the-jewels</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-020-run-the-jewels/all-my-favorite-songs-020-run-the-jewels.mp3" length="288903382" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-020-run-the-jewels/all-my-favorite-songs-020-run-the-jewels.jpg' />
                <description>Run the Jewels, also known by the initialism RTJ, is an American hip hop super-duo composed of Brooklyn-based rapper and producer El-P, and Atlanta-based rapper Killer Mike. Atop hard-hitting beats and ominous production, the pair trade aggressive and often wryly comical rhymes, touching upon social issues, life and death, and a heavy dose of chest-thumping bragging.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode, part two of a series of two, all songs selected by Run The Jewels as guest for Australian TV show Rage, on March 21 2015.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Aesop Rock, John Darnielle of The Mountain Goats, Dungeon Family, CeeLo Green, Outkast, Big Gipp, Backbone, Purple Ribbon And Big Boi, Yelawolf, Bun B, Rick Ross, Lil Wayne, clipping., Mariel Jacoda, Freddie Gibbs, Madlib, Young Thug, A$AP Ferg, Madvillain, MF DOOM, BADBADNOTGOOD, Ghostface Killah, Ratking, RATKING, Mitski, Pictureplane, Death Grips, Passion Pit, TOTO, The Cranberries, The Strokes, Matt and Kim, The Cure, Will Smith, Pras Michel, Ol&#39; DB, LCD Soundsystem, Wham!, Paul Simon, Björk, Bobby McFerrin, Other Lives, Grimes, Celestial Shore, Winterplan, Hound , LA Priest, The Very Best, Hermitude, TAPZ, Kagu, Tropics, Courtney Barnett, Tear Council, Flight Facilities, All We Are, Blur</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 019 by Run The Jewels - Rage Guest (part 1 of 2)</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#019</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-019-run-the-jewels</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-019-run-the-jewels/all-my-favorite-songs-019-run-the-jewels.mp3" length="277430930" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-019-run-the-jewels/all-my-favorite-songs-019-run-the-jewels.jpg' />
                <description>Run the Jewels, also known by the initialism RTJ, is an American hip hop super-duo composed of Brooklyn-based rapper and producer El-P, and Atlanta-based rapper Killer Mike. Atop hard-hitting beats and ominous production, the pair trade aggressive and often wryly comical rhymes, touching upon social issues, life and death, and a heavy dose of chest-thumping bragging.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode, part one of a series of two, all songs selected by Run The Jewels as guest for Australian TV show Rage, on March 21 2015.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Run The Jewels, Earl Sweatshirt, Action Bronson, Talib Kweli, The Game, 50 Cent, T.I., Young Thug, BOOTS, Portishead, Massive Attack, Wavves, Adam Sandler, Jimi Hendriz, Outkast, Nas, JAY-Z, DMX, Rage Against The Machine, Faith No More, Led Zeppelin, The Notorious B.I.G., N.W.A., Snoop Dogg, Daz Dillinger, Wilder Zoby, Flying Lotus, D&#39;Angelo, Gravediggaz, Ghostface Killah, Raekwon, Cappadonna, Rick Ross, Danny Brown, Tyler, The Creator, Cut Killer, Mos Def, Joey Bada$$, Scarface, Ice Cube, Devin The Dude, Big Mike, Wu-Tang Clan, ODB, Inspectah Deck, Method Man, U-God, RZA, GZA, Masta Killa, 2 Pac, Warren G, Nate Dogg, Zola Jesus, Lorde, Beastie Boys, El-P, Trent Reznor, Killer Mike, Bun B, Trouble, Big Boi, Outkast Featuring Killer Mike And Sleepy Brown, Company Flow, Aesop Rock</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 01:23:45 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 018 by PJ Harvey - 11 12 13 14</title>
                <link>https://allmyfavoritesongs.com#018</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-018-pj-harvey</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-018-pj-harvey/all-my-favorite-songs-018-pj-harvey.mp3" length="283340555" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-018-pj-harvey/all-my-favorite-songs-018-pj-harvey.jpg' />
                <description>Polly Jean Harvey (born 9 October 1969) is an English singer, songwriter and musician. Primarily known as a vocalist and guitarist, she is also proficient with a wide range of instruments. Over the course of her career, Harvey established herself as one of the most individual and influential songwriters of her era, exploring themes of sex, religion, and political issues with unnerving honesty, dark humor, and a twisted theatricality.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This episode is a compilation of the four playlists published by Harvey between August 2019 and August 2021.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Claude Debussy, Martin Jones, Colin Stetson, Amen Dunes, Empire of the Sun, Ólafur Arnalds, Nils Frahm, Captain Beefheart &amp; His Magic Band, Connan Mockasin, Thom Yorke, Coby Sey, Bendik Giske, Tirzah, Sarah Neufeld, Big Thief, Hekla, Sibylle Baier, Nick Cave &amp; The Bad Seeds, Desert Sessions, Liela Moss, slowthai, Mura Masa, Eartheater, Hole, Radiohead, Nicholas Britell, Hanan Townshend, Here We Go Magic, Mark Lanegan, Bob Dylan, Anne Briggs, Stina Nordenstam, Jed Kurzel, SAULT, Michael Kiwanuka, Martin Phipps, Johnny Flynn, Robert Macfarlane, Low, Sleaford Mods, Superstate, Graham Coxon, Valentina Pappalardo, Shabazz Palaces</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 017 by David Bowie - 25 Favorite Albums</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#017</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-017-david-bowie</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-017-david-bowie/all-my-favorite-songs-017-david-bowie.mp3" length="281438811" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-017-david-bowie/all-my-favorite-songs-017-david-bowie.jpg' />
                <description>David Robert Jones (8 January 1947 – 10 January 2016), known professionally as David Bowie, was an English singer-songwriter and actor. A leading figure in the music industry, Bowie is regarded as one of the most influential musicians of the 20th century. He was acclaimed by critics and musicians, particularly for his innovative work during the 1970s. His career was marked by reinvention and visual presentation, and his music and stagecraft had a significant impact on popular music.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode we selected two tracks from each of the 25 records Bowie revealed were his favorite to Vanity Fair, for their November 2003 issue.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; The Last Poets, Robert Wyatt, Little Richard, Steve Reich, The Velvet Underground, Nico, John Lee Hooker, Ray Koerner &amp; Glover, James Brown, Linton Kwesi Johnson, The Red Flower Of Tachai Blossoms Everywhere, Daevid Allen, Scott Walker, Tom Dissevelt, Kid Baltan, The Incredible String Band, Tucker Zimmerman, Richard Strauss, Gundula Janowitz, Berliner Philharmoniker, Herbert von Karajan, Glenn Branca, Syd Barrett, George Crumb, Kronos Quartet, Toots &amp; The Maytals, Harry Partch, John Stannard, Victoria Bond, Paul Bergen, Ensemble of Unique Instruments, Danlee Mitchell, Charles Mingus, Igor Stravinsky, Columbia Symphony Orchestra, The Fugs, Anatoly Lyadov, Florence Foster Jenkins, Cosme McMoon</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 016 by Kurt Cobain - Top 50 Albums</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#016</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-016-kurt-cobain</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-016-kurt-cobain/all-my-favorite-songs-016-kurt-cobain.mp3" length="251341055" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-016-kurt-cobain/all-my-favorite-songs-016-kurt-cobain.jpg' />
                <description>Kurt Donald Cobain (February 20, 1967 – c. April 5, 1994) was an American singer, songwriter, artist and musician. He was the frontman of the rock band Nirvana, serving as the band&#39;s guitarist, lead vocalist, and primary songwriter. Through his angst-fueled songwriting and anti-establishment persona, Cobain&#39;s compositions widened the thematic conventions of mainstream rock music. He was often heralded as a spokesman of Generation X and is considered to be one of the most influential musicians in the history of alternative rock.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This episode is based on Kurt&#39;s handwritten list of Top 50 albums, as featured in the 2002 anthology Journals. Note we included a song from each side of The Faith/Void split LP which brings our song total to 51.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; The Stooges, Pixies, The Breeders, The Vaselines, The Shaggs, Fang, MDC, Scratch Acid, Saccharine Trust, Butthole Surfers, Black Flag, Bad Brains, Gang Of Four, Sex Pistols, The Frogs, PJ Harvey, Sonic Youth, The Knack, The Saints, Kleenex, The Raincoats, Young Marble Giants, Aerosmith, Germs, R.E.M., Shonen Knife, The Slits, The Clash, The Faith, Void, Rites of Spring, Beat Happening, Tales Of Terror, Lead Belly, Mudhoney, Daniel Johnston, Flipper, The Beatles, Half Japanese, Fear, Public Image Ltd., Public Enemy, Marine Girls, David Bowie, Wipers, Mazzy Star, Swans</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 015 by Buzz Osborne - Bands that were good, but blew it</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#015</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-015-buzz-osborne</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-015-buzz-osborne/all-my-favorite-songs-015-buzz-osborne.mp3" length="178448566" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-015-buzz-osborne/all-my-favorite-songs-015-buzz-osborne.jpg' />
                <description>Roger &#39;Buzz&#39; Osborne (born March 25, 1964), also known as King Buzzo, is an American guitarist, vocalist and songwriter. He is a founding member of the Melvins, as well as Fantômas and Venomous Concept. As founder of the Melvins, Buzz Osborne was one of the most influential figures in alternative rock during the 1980s and &#39;90s and continued to produce a fascinating body of work well into the new millennium, though his impact often came second-hand.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Osborne&#39;s massive, often sludgy guitar tone and bulldozer melodic structures were a major influence on the rise of the grunge scene in the Pacific Northwest as well as later varieties of off-center heavy rock, and as a mentor to his friend Kurt Cobain, Osborne helped guide Nirvana&#39;s early sound, and his importance was often cited by Cobain after Nevermind made him a major star.   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode Buzz&#39;s A.V. Club January 7 2014 mixtape, of &#39;bands that were good, but blew it&#39;.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; ISIS, The Rolling Stones, Metallica, Black Flag, The Who, Hüsker Dü, The Replacements, Jimi Hendrix, Cows, The Birthday Party</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 014 by Steve Albini - Rage Guest (part 2 of 2)</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#014</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-014-steve-albini</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-014-steve-albini/all-my-favorite-songs-014-steve-albini.mp3" length="348034666" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-014-steve-albini/all-my-favorite-songs-014-steve-albini.jpg' />
                <description>Steve Albini (born July 22, 1961) is an American musician, record producer, audio engineer and music journalist. He was a member of Big Black, Rapeman and Flour, and is a member of Shellac. He is the founder, owner and principal engineer of Electrical Audio, a recording studio complex in Chicago. In 2018, Albini estimated that he had worked on several thousand albums over his career. He has worked with acts such as Nirvana, Pixies, the Breeders and PJ Harvey. Albini is also known for his outspoken views on the music industry, having stated repeatedly that it financially exploits artists and homogenizes their sound, as well as the flaws in the digital recording process and the superiority of analog technology.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Albini&#39;s engineering skills have been celebrated for their sense of space, naturalistic tone, and the power of his guitar and drum sounds; his own guitar work is as imaginatively abrasive as his lyrics, which can be challenging and sometimes confrontational. Nearly alone among well-known producers and musicians, Albini refuses to take ongoing royalties from album sales, feeling that a producer&#39;s job is to record the music to the band&#39;s desires, and that paying producers as if they had contributed artistically to an album is unethical.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode, part two of a series of two, all songs selected by Steve Albini as guest for Australian TV show Rage, on June 29 2013.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Bill Withers, Stevie Wonder, Repercussions, Curtis Mayfield, Philip Glass, Broadcast, Chrome, Sisters of Mercy, Venom P. Stinger, Killing Joke, Meshuggah, U.S. Maple, Smog, Mariachi El Bronx, Pikelet, The Angels, ACDC, ZZ Top, Buckcherry, Pretenders, The Kinks, Sweet, Turbonegro, Lubricated Goat, Budd, Brujeria, Sepultura, Bad Brains, The Residents, Sparklehorse, Swans, Dead Moon, Minutemen, R.L. Burnside, Randy Newman, Low, A Certain Ratio, Bo Diddley, Canned Heat, Palace Music, Screaming Trees, Slade, The Who, Buzzcocks, Spiritualized, Purplene, Scout Niblett, Cheer Accident, Big Black, The Specials, Leonard Cohen, Kraftwerk, The Saints, The Stranglers, Wire, High Dependency Unit, Boards of Canada, The White Stripes, Stiff Little Fingers, Motörhead, Ramones, Brian Eno, John Cale, Queen</description>
                <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 013 by Steve Albini - Rage Guest (part 1 of 2)</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#013</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-013-steve-albini</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-013-steve-albini/all-my-favorite-songs-013-steve-albini.mp3" length="307323556" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-013-steve-albini/all-my-favorite-songs-013-steve-albini.jpg' />
                <description>Steve Albini (born July 22, 1961) is an American musician, record producer, audio engineer and music journalist. He was a member of Big Black, Rapeman and Flour, and is a member of Shellac. He is the founder, owner and principal engineer of Electrical Audio, a recording studio complex in Chicago. In 2018, Albini estimated that he had worked on several thousand albums over his career. He has worked with acts such as Nirvana, Pixies, the Breeders and PJ Harvey. Albini is also known for his outspoken views on the music industry, having stated repeatedly that it financially exploits artists and homogenizes their sound, as well as the flaws in the digital recording process and the superiority of analog technology.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Albini&#39;s engineering skills have been celebrated for their sense of space, naturalistic tone, and the power of his guitar and drum sounds; his own guitar work is as imaginatively abrasive as his lyrics, which can be challenging and sometimes confrontational. Nearly alone among well-known producers and musicians, Albini refuses to take ongoing royalties from album sales, feeling that a producer&#39;s job is to record the music to the band&#39;s desires, and that paying producers as if they had contributed artistically to an album is unethical.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode, part one of a series of two, all songs selected by Steve Albini as guest for Australian TV show Rage, on June 29 2013.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; The B-52&#39;s, Blondie, The Stranglers, Man Or Astro-Man, Chad Van Gaalen, Lou Reed, The Specials, The Cars, Siouxsie and the Banshees, D. Rider, Superchunk, The Breeders, Andrew Bird, Angus &amp; Julia Stone, Björk, A1 People, Pete Shelley, Cheap Trick, Big Black, Altered Images, Pere Ubu, Sonic Youth, Bailter Space, Useless ID, Alan Vega, Bauhaus, Toys Went Berserk, Charge Group, Tortoise, Cat Power, The Only Ones, Black Box Recorder, The Human League, Tubeway Army, Kraftwerk, Xiu Xiu, Plastic Bertrand, Mucca Pazza, Radio Birdman, Ted Leo and the Pharmacists, The Bronx, Mclusky, Public Image Ltd., Sex Pistols, X-Ray Spex, Alice Cooper, Neil Young, Crazy Horse, Willie Nelson, The Birthday Party, Dead Meadow, Red Fang, Archers Of Loaf, The Amps, Dead Rider, Har Mar Superstar, Beth Ditto, CeeLo Green</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 012 by Adam Yauch - Mixtape</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#012</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-012-adam-yauch</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-012-adam-yauch/all-my-favorite-songs-012-adam-yauch.mp3" length="251686342" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-012-adam-yauch/all-my-favorite-songs-012-adam-yauch.jpg' />
                <description>Adam Nathaniel Yauch (August 5, 1964 – May 4, 2012), better known under the stage name MCA, was an American rapper, bass player, filmmaker and a founding member of the hip hop group Beastie Boys. Yauch co-founded the Beastie Boys with Mike &#39;Mike D&#39; Diamond and Adam &#39;Ad-Rock&#39; Horovitz in 1979. The band started off as a hardcore punk group, but soon began experimenting with hip-hop. The band broke huge with their first proper album, Licensed to Ill, in 1986; it was the biggest-selling rap album of the decade and the first to reach Number One on the Billboard chart. Further albums Paul’s Boutique, Check Your Head and Ill Communication cemented the Beasties as a true superstar act. Yauch also directed many of the Beastie Boys’ music videos under the pseudonym Nathaniel Hornblower. In 2002, he founded Oscilloscope Laboratories, an independent film production and distribution company based in New York City. As a Buddhist, he was involved in the Tibetan independence movement and organized the Tibetan Freedom Concert. He died in 2012 from parotid cancer.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Bad Brains, Stiff Little Fingers, Buzzcocks, Generation X, Public Image Ltd., Toots &amp; The Maytals, Linton Kwesi Johnson, Bob Marley &amp; The Wailers, Spoonie Gee, Run–D.M.C., Bob Dylan, Public Enemy, Jimi Hendrix, Jackson Browne, Back Door, The Beatles, Elis Regina, Antônio Carlos Jobim, Kanye West, Mos Def, Freeway, The Boys Choir Of Harlem, Phoenix, The Slits, Killing Joke, New Age Steppers, Young Marble Giants, Minor Threat, Cockney Rejects, Dr. Jeckyll &amp; Mr. Hyde, Grandmaster Flash &amp; The Furious Five, Jocelyn Brown, Frederick M.C. Count Linton, Malcolm McLaren, The Crusaders, Larry Carlton, Beanie Sigel, The Strokes, Arctic Monkeys</description>
                <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 011 by Thurston Moore - Favorite Songs Of All Time</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#011</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-011-thurston-moore</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-011-thurston-moore/all-my-favorite-songs-011-thurston-moore.mp3" length="226106281" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-011-thurston-moore/all-my-favorite-songs-011-thurston-moore.jpg' />
                <description>Thurston Joseph Moore (born July 25, 1958) is an American musician best known as a member of Sonic Youth. He has also participated in many solo and group collaborations outside Sonic Youth, as well as running the Ecstatic Peace! record label. Thurston Moore&#39;s work with Sonic Youth rearranged the parameters of indie rock to an almost incalculable degree, merging experimental art rock tendencies with unconventional guitar tunings for a sound that would influence generations to come. Moore&#39;s abstract poetic lyrics and perpetually mysterious aura were core ingredients of Sonic Youth&#39;s 30-plus-year run, but also bled into countless side projects and less-frequent solo albums like 1994&#39;s sprawling and loose Psychic Hearts. After the group&#39;s breakup in 2011, Moore continued with his ambitions, ranging from projects like his band Chelsea Light Moving to noisy collaborations with Merzbow and John Zorn to solo albums like 2020&#39;s By the Fire that continued exploring the kind of moody, twisting art rock he&#39;d become an icon of with Sonic Youth. Moore was ranked 34th in Rolling Stone&#39;s 2004 edition of the &#39;100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time.&#39; In May 2012, Spin published a staff-selected list of the top 100 rock guitarists, and ranked Moore and his Sonic Youth bandmate Lee Ranaldo together at number 1.   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Tapper Zukie, Patti Smith, Teenage Jesus &amp; The Jerks, MARS, Public Image Ltd., The Slits, The Raincoats, Captain Beefheart &amp; His Magic Band, Alice Cooper, T. Rex, Archie Shepp, Billie Holiday, Teddy Wilson, Nirvana, Mudhoney, Dinosaur Jr., Jackson C. Frank, Bush Tetras, Germs, Boredoms, Lou Reed, The Beach Boys, David Bowie, Sparks, Siouxsie and the Banshees, The Damned, The Mentally Ill, Minor Threat, Black Flag, The Untouchables, Iron Cross, The Faith, Void, Negative Approach, Youth Brigade, S.O.A., Anne Briggs, The Fugs, Jimi Hendrix</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 010 by Mike Patton - Playlist for Henry Rollins</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#010</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-010-mike-patton</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-010-mike-patton/all-my-favorite-songs-010-mike-patton.mp3" length="116232555" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-010-mike-patton/all-my-favorite-songs-010-mike-patton.jpg' />
                <description>Michael Allan Patton (born January 27, 1968) is an American singer, producer, film composer and voice actor, best known as the lead vocalist of the alternative metal band Faith No More. Noted for his vocal proficiency, diverse singing techniques, wide range of projects, style-transcending influences, eccentric public image and contempt for the music industry, Patton has earned critical praise and influenced many contemporary singers. One of the most versatile, innately talented, and idiosyncratic singers in rock music, Mike Patton is also one of the genre&#39;s most valuable players, since he has divided his time between a host of diverse projects including Faith No More, Mr. Bungle, Fantômas, Tomahawk, Peeping Tom, Nevermen, Dead Cross, and an experimental solo career. In addition to his band and solo work, Patton is a gifted actor and producer who has collaborated with a wide array of artists, including John Zorn, Sepultura, Melvins, Melt Banana, and Kool Keith.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Bad Brains, Don Black, John Barry, Tom Jones, Young Fathers, Quincy Jones, Don Elliott, Terveet Kädet, Dead Cross, Jacques Brel, Tom Dissevelt, White Noise, Charlie Parr, Messer Chups, João Gilberto, Funkadelic, Die Kreuzen, Adriano Celentano, Conlon Nancarrow, Bösendorfer Grand Piano, Dion Mcgregor, Basil Kirchin, Chet Baker, Nino Rota, Sun Ra, The Cosmic Rays</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 009 by Slipknot - Halloween Playlist</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#009</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-009-slipknot</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-009-slipknot/all-my-favorite-songs-009-slipknot.mp3" length="221642630" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-009-slipknot/all-my-favorite-songs-009-slipknot.jpg' />
                <description>Slipknot is an American heavy metal band formed in Des Moines, Iowa, in 1995 by percussionist Shawn Crahan, drummer Joey Jordison and bassist Paul Gray. After several lineup changes in its early years, the band settled on nine members for more than a decade: Crahan, Jordison, Gray, Craig Jones, Mick Thomson, Corey Taylor, Sid Wilson, Chris Fehn, and Jim Root. Gray died on May 24, 2010, and was replaced during 2011–2014 by guitarist Donnie Steele. Slipknot&#39;s mix of grinding, post-Korn alternative metal, Marilyn Manson-esque neo-shock rock, and rap-metal helped make them one of the most popular bands in the nu-metal explosion of the late 1990s and early 2000s. But even more helpful was their theatrical, attention-grabbing image: the band always performed in identical industrial jump suits and homemade Halloween masks, and added to their mysterious anonymity by adopting the numbers zero through eight as stage aliases. Add to that a lyrical preoccupation with darkness and nihilism, and an affectionately insulting name for their fans (&#39;Maggots&#39;), and Slipknot&#39;s blueprint for nu-metal success was set.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Slipknot, Talking Heads, S.O.D. Stormtroopers of Death, Dangerous Toys, Iron Maiden, Ho99o9, Refused, Public Enemy, Marilyn Manson, White Zombie, Slayer, Venom, Megadeth, Ice Cube, Dr. Dre, Misfits, Glenn Danzig, Black Sabbath, Judas Priest, Testament, Alice Cooper, Behemoth, Neurosis, Mötley Crüe, Concrete Blonde, W.A.S.P.</description>
                <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 008 by Kurt Vile - Nepotismic Reticulum Top Faves Studio Mixtape</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#008</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-008-kurt-vile</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-008-kurt-vile/all-my-favorite-songs-008-kurt-vile.mp3" length="303395352" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-008-kurt-vile/all-my-favorite-songs-008-kurt-vile.jpg' />
                <description>Kurt Samuel Vile (born January 3, 1980) is an American singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, and record producer. He is known for his solo work and as the former lead guitarist of rock band The War on Drugs. Both in the studio and during live performances, Vile is accompanied by his backing band, The Violators, which currently includes Jesse Trbovich (bass, guitar, saxophone), Rob Laakso (guitar, bass) and Kyle Spence (drums). His laid-back and drifting indie rock takes notes from masters like Neil Young, Sonic Youth, and Dinosaur Jr., exploring inventive guitar tones on meditative and often self-reflective songs.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Stephen Malkmus &amp; The Jicks, Courtney Barnett, DRINKS, Cass McCombs, John Prine, Nathan Bowles, Grouper, Yo La Tengo, Jessica Pratt, Steve Gunn, Kurt Vile, Steely Dan, The Go-Betweens, Nick Cave &amp; The Bad Seeds, Suicide, The Move, Captain Beefheart, Miles Davis, The Sadies, The Pogues, The Rolling Stones, Rusty Kershaw, Doug Kershaw, Willie Dunn, Aphrodite&#39;s Child, Lou Reed, Prince, Depeche Mode, David Bowie, Big Star, Flamin&#39; Groovies, The Byrds, Tim Buckley, Randy Newman, David Byrne, Gary Numan  Tubeway Army</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 007 by SebastiAn - Picks</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#007</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-007-sebastian</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-007-sebastian/all-my-favorite-songs-007-sebastian.mp3" length="277264660" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-007-sebastian/all-my-favorite-songs-007-sebastian.jpg' />
                <description>Sébastien Akchoté-Bozović (born 3 February 1981), known mononymously as Sebastian (stylised as SebastiAn), is a French musician, composer, producer, mixer, engineer, vocalist and DJ affiliated with Ed Banger Records. He has worked as a solo electronic musician and as a remixer for bands and singers such as Charlotte Gainsbourg, Daft Punk, Beastie Boys, Bloc Party, and Nero. He has also composed and produced songs for Charlotte Gainsbourg, Katerine, Kavinsky, Frank Ocean, Uffie and Woodkid, and he has composed soundtracks for the films Our Day Will Come, The World Is Yours and Steak (in which he also acted, credited under the name Sebastian Akchoté). Many of his tracks have been used on television and in video games.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; SebastiAn, Syd, Gary Numan, Bakar, Iggy Pop, Bon Iver, Gallant, Jhené Aiko, A. K. Paul, Mica Levi, Jackson And His Computer Band, TOBACCO, Beck, Frank Ocean, The Waitresses, JPEGMAFIA, Mr. Oizo, Phra, Daft Punk, Sparks, Kavinsky, Lightning Bolt, Chassol, Prince, Mother&#39;s Finest, The Beach Boys, Chet Baker, The Marketts, Mark Bell, Errorsmith, Orchestre Lamoureux, DJ Mehdi, Thomas Roussel, Aphex Twin, Billie Holiday, Catherine Deneuve, Kanye West, PARTYNEXTDOOR, Googoosh, Charlotte Gainsbourg, Ennio Morricone, Hrvoje Hitrec, Wings</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 006 by Wu-Tang Clan - Music Mondays</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#006</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-006-wu-tang-clan</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-006-wu-tang-clan/all-my-favorite-songs-006-wu-tang-clan.mp3" length="130190445" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-006-wu-tang-clan/all-my-favorite-songs-006-wu-tang-clan.jpg' />
                <description>Wu-Tang Clan is an American hip hop group formed in Staten Island, New York City, in 1992. Its original members include RZA, GZA, Ol&#39; Dirty Bastard, Method Man, Raekwon, Ghostface Killah, Inspectah Deck, U-God, and Masta Killa. Close affiliate Cappadonna later became an official member. Wu-Tang Clan are regarded as a highly influential group in hip hop, helping to popularize and develop the East Coast hip hop and hardcore hip hop styles.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Method Man, Wu-Tang Clan, RZA, Inspectah Deck, Raekwon, Ghostface Killah, Cappadonna, Mobb Deep, ODB, The Notorious B.I.G., Gang Starr, U-God, GZA, Masta Killa, GZA (Genius), Nas, Onyx, Ice Cube, Warren G, Nate Dogg, The Pharcyde</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 005 by Nick Cave - Hiding Songs</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#005</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-005-nick-cave</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-005-nick-cave/all-my-favorite-songs-005-nick-cave.mp3" length="108547138" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-005-nick-cave/all-my-favorite-songs-005-nick-cave.jpg' />
                <description>Nicholas Edward Cave AO (born 22 September 1957) is an Australian singer, songwriter, author, screenwriter, composer and occasional actor. Known for his baritone voice and for fronting the rock band Nick Cave and the Bad Seeds, Cave&#39;s music is generally characterised by emotional intensity, a wide variety of influences and lyrical obsessions with death, religion, love and violence.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Since the late &#39;70s, Nick Cave has proved to be one of the most enduring talents to emerge from the post-punk era. In addition to being a remarkably consistent recording artist, his songs have been covered by everyone from Josh Groban, PJ Harvey, and Johnny Cash to Arctic Monkeys, Metallica, and Chelsea Wolfe, to name a few.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Leonard Cohen, Karen Dalton, Neil Young, John Lee Hooker, Van Morrison, Bob Dylan, Nina Simone, Big Star, Brian Eno, Bill Callahan, The Gun Club</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 004 by Viagra Boys - Shrimptech Enterprises Vol.1</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#004</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-004-viagra-boys</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-004-viagra-boys/all-my-favorite-songs-004-viagra-boys.mp3" length="305630792" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-004-viagra-boys/all-my-favorite-songs-004-viagra-boys.jpg' />
                <description>Viagra Boys are a Swedish post-punk band from Stockholm. The band was formed in 2015, with several members coming from the bands Les Big Byrd, Pig Eyes, Nine, Nitad and Neu-Ronz. In 2018, they released their first album, Street Worms. Nils Hansson, a journalist at the newspaper Dagens Nyheter described the band favorably, praising their musical style, as well as their use of black humor and satire, and rated the album a five out of five. In 2019, the band won the Independent Music Companies Association (IMPALA) Album of the Year Award for Street Worms. The band&#39;s second album, Welfare Jazz, was released in January 2021.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Tubeway Army, The Jesus and Mary Chain, Chain and The Gang, DEVO, Goran Kajfes Subtropic Arkestra, Goran Kajfes, Roxy Music, Built To Spill, The Stooges, Waylon Jennings, Clap Your Hands Say Yeah, DAF, Broadcast, Container, Run The Jewels, Spacemen 3, Daniel Lanois, Anna Domino, Rocket From The Tombs, Esbjörn Svensson Trio, Missing Persons, Pere Ubu, Christian Scott aTunde Adjuah, Elena Pinderhughes, Tom Tom Club, 13th Floor Elevators, Sleaford Mods, John Coltrane, Art Ensemble Of Chicago, Pixies, Fire! Orchestra, Richard Hell, The Breeders, Daniel Ögren, Sam Rivers, Chris &amp; Cosey, The Soft Boys, Hawkwind, Joni Mitchell</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 003 by Drive Like Jehu - All Tomorrow's Parties 2.0</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#003</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-003-drive-like-jehu</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-003-drive-like-jehu/all-my-favorite-songs-003-drive-like-jehu.mp3" length="141259537" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-003-drive-like-jehu/all-my-favorite-songs-003-drive-like-jehu.jpg' />
                <description>Drive Like Jehu was an American post-hardcore band from San Diego active from 1990 to 1995. It was formed by rhythm guitarist and vocalist Rick Froberg and lead guitarist John Reis, ex-members of Pitchfork, along with bassist Mike Kennedy and drummer Mark Trombino, both from Night Soil Man, after their two bands disbanded in 1990. Drive Like Jehu&#39;s music was characterized by passionate singing, unusual song structure, indirect melodic themes, intricate guitar playing, and calculated use of tension, resulting in a distinctive sound amongst other post-hardcore acts and helped to catalyze the evolution of hardcore punk into emo.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode all songs by bands selected by Drive Like Jehu to play All Tomorrow&#39;s Parties 2.0 April 22-24, 2016.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Hot Snakes, The Blind Shake, Mrs. Magician, Flamin&#39; Groovies, The King Khan &amp; BBQ Show, The Schizophonics, Metz, Mission Of Burma, The Gories, King Khan and the Shrines, The Spits, Rocket From The Crypt, Betunizer, The Monkeywrench, Holly Golightly, Dan Sartain, Martin Rev, Tortoise, The Ex, PyPy, Gary Wilson, Claw Hammer, Wau y Los Arrrghs</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 002 by Dinosaur Jr. - 80's Inspirations</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#002</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-002-dinosaur-jr</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-002-dinosaur-jr/all-my-favorite-songs-002-dinosaur-jr.mp3" length="87131551" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-002-dinosaur-jr/all-my-favorite-songs-002-dinosaur-jr.jpg' />
                <description>Dinosaur Jr. is an American rock band formed in Amherst, Massachusetts, in 1984, originally simply called Dinosaur until legal issues forced a change in name. The band was founded by J Mascis (guitar, vocals, primary songwriter), Lou Barlow (bass, vocals), and Murph (drums). After three albums on independent labels, the band earned a reputation as one of the formative influences on American alternative rock. Mascis&#39;s drawling vocals and distinct guitar sound, hearkening back to 1960s and 1970s classic rock and characterized by extensive use of feedback and distortion, were highly influential in the alternative rock movement of the 1990s.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Wipers, The Dream Syndicate, True West, The Jesus and Mary Chain, The Birthday Party, Throbbing Gristle, Venom, Accept, Saint Vitus, The Eastern Dark, The Neats, Green On Red, Meat Puppets</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 001 by Weezer - All My Favorite Songs</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#001</link>
                <guid>https://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-001-weezer</guid>
                <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-001-weezer/all-my-favorite-songs-001-weezer.mp3" length="55457251" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='https://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-001-weezer/all-my-favorite-songs-001-weezer.jpg' />
                <description>Weezer is an American rock band formed in Los Angeles, California, in 1992. Since 2001, the band has consisted of Rivers Cuomo (lead vocals, lead guitar, keyboards), Patrick Wilson (drums, percussion, backing vocals), Brian Bell (guitar, backing vocals, keyboards), and Scott Shriner (bass, backing vocals, keyboards).  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Neil Young, REO Speedwagon, Johnny Cash, Toni Braxton, Yeah Yeah Yeahs, Céline Dion, Sinéad O&#39;Connor</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

</channel>

</rss>

