<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:content='http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/' xmlns:googleplay='http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0' xmlns:itunes='http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd' version='2.0'>

<channel>
        <atom:link href='http://feeds.feedburner.com/all-my-favorite-songs' rel='self' type='application/rss+xml' />
        <title>All My Favorite Songs</title>
        <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com</link>
        <description>Have you ever been curious, as to what music others listen to? All My Favorite Songs is a podcast of uninterrupted music, exclusively curated by others, and dug up from hidden unexpected places.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 22:20:17 +0100</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>&#xA9; 2021 A Bee MC</copyright>
        <ttl>60</ttl>
        <image>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com</link>
                <url>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com/img/all-my-favorite-songs.jpg</url>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs</title>
        </image>
        <itunes:image href='http://allmyfavoritesongs.com/img/all-my-favorite-songs.jpg' />
        <itunes:subtitle>Have you ever been curious, as to what music others listen to? All My Favorite Songs is a podcast of uninterrupted music, exclusively curated by others, and dug up from hidden unexpected places.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Have you ever been curious, as to what music others listen to? All My Favorite Songs is a podcast of uninterrupted music, exclusively curated by others, and dug up from hidden unexpected places.</itunes:summary>        
        <itunes:category text='Music' />
        <itunes:keywords>all, favorite, songs, podcast, music</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:author>A Bee MC</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
                <itunes:name>A Bee MC</itunes:name>
                <itunes:email>abmc@gmx.net</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type>



        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 014 by Steve Albini - Rage Guest (part 2 of 2)</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#014</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-014-steve-albini</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-014-steve-albini/all-my-favorite-songs-014-steve-albini.mp3" length="348034666" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-014-steve-albini/all-my-favorite-songs-014-steve-albini.jpg' />
                <description>Steve Albini (born July 22, 1961) is an American musician, record producer, audio engineer and music journalist. He was a member of Big Black, Rapeman and Flour, and is a member of Shellac. He is the founder, owner and principal engineer of Electrical Audio, a recording studio complex in Chicago. In 2018, Albini estimated that he had worked on several thousand albums over his career. He has worked with acts such as Nirvana, Pixies, the Breeders and PJ Harvey. Albini is also known for his outspoken views on the music industry, having stated repeatedly that it financially exploits artists and homogenizes their sound, as well as the flaws in the digital recording process and the superiority of analog technology.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Albini&#39;s engineering skills have been celebrated for their sense of space, naturalistic tone, and the power of his guitar and drum sounds; his own guitar work is as imaginatively abrasive as his lyrics, which can be challenging and sometimes confrontational. Nearly alone among well-known producers and musicians, Albini refuses to take ongoing royalties from album sales, feeling that a producer&#39;s job is to record the music to the band&#39;s desires, and that paying producers as if they had contributed artistically to an album is unethical.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode, part two of a series of two, all songs selected by Steve Albini as guest for Australian TV show Rage, on June 29 2013.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Bill Withers, Stevie Wonder, Repercussions, Curtis Mayfield, Philip Glass, Broadcast, Chrome, Sisters of Mercy, Venom P. Stinger, Killing Joke, Meshuggah, U.S. Maple, Smog, Mariachi El Bronx, Pikelet, The Angels, ACDC, ZZ Top, Buckcherry, Pretenders, The Kinks, Sweet, Turbonegro, Lubricated Goat, Budd, Brujeria, Sepultura, Bad Brains, The Residents, Sparklehorse, Swans, Dead Moon, Minutemen, R.L. Burnside, Randy Newman, Low, A Certain Ratio, Bo Diddley, Canned Heat, Palace Music, Screaming Trees, Slade, The Who, Buzzcocks, Spiritualized, Purplene, Scout Niblett, Cheer Accident, Big Black, The Specials, Leonard Cohen, Kraftwerk, The Saints, The Stranglers, Wire, High Dependency Unit, Boards of Canada, The White Stripes, Stiff Little Fingers, Motörhead, Ramones, Brian Eno, John Cale, Queen</description>
                <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 013 by Steve Albini - Rage Guest (part 1 of 2)</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#013</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-013-steve-albini</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-013-steve-albini/all-my-favorite-songs-013-steve-albini.mp3" length="307323556" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-013-steve-albini/all-my-favorite-songs-013-steve-albini.jpg' />
                <description>Steve Albini (born July 22, 1961) is an American musician, record producer, audio engineer and music journalist. He was a member of Big Black, Rapeman and Flour, and is a member of Shellac. He is the founder, owner and principal engineer of Electrical Audio, a recording studio complex in Chicago. In 2018, Albini estimated that he had worked on several thousand albums over his career. He has worked with acts such as Nirvana, Pixies, the Breeders and PJ Harvey. Albini is also known for his outspoken views on the music industry, having stated repeatedly that it financially exploits artists and homogenizes their sound, as well as the flaws in the digital recording process and the superiority of analog technology.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Albini&#39;s engineering skills have been celebrated for their sense of space, naturalistic tone, and the power of his guitar and drum sounds; his own guitar work is as imaginatively abrasive as his lyrics, which can be challenging and sometimes confrontational. Nearly alone among well-known producers and musicians, Albini refuses to take ongoing royalties from album sales, feeling that a producer&#39;s job is to record the music to the band&#39;s desires, and that paying producers as if they had contributed artistically to an album is unethical.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode, part one of a series of two, all songs selected by Steve Albini as guest for Australian TV show Rage, on June 29 2013.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; The B-52&#39;s, Blondie, The Stranglers, Man Or Astro-Man, Chad Van Gaalen, Lou Reed, The Specials, The Cars, Siouxsie and the Banshees, D. Rider, Superchunk, The Breeders, Andrew Bird, Angus &amp; Julia Stone, Björk, A1 People, Pete Shelley, Cheap Trick, Big Black, Altered Images, Pere Ubu, Sonic Youth, Bailter Space, Useless ID, Alan Vega, Bauhaus, Toys Went Berserk, Charge Group, Tortoise, Cat Power, The Only Ones, Black Box Recorder, The Human League, Tubeway Army, Kraftwerk, Xiu Xiu, Plastic Bertrand, Mucca Pazza, Radio Birdman, Ted Leo and the Pharmacists, The Bronx, Mclusky, Public Image Ltd., Sex Pistols, X-Ray Spex, Alice Cooper, Neil Young, Crazy Horse, Willie Nelson, The Birthday Party, Dead Meadow, Red Fang, Archers Of Loaf, The Amps, Dead Rider, Har Mar Superstar, Beth Ditto, CeeLo Green</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 012 by Adam Yauch - Mixtape</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#012</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-012-adam-yauch</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-012-adam-yauch/all-my-favorite-songs-012-adam-yauch.mp3" length="251686342" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-012-adam-yauch/all-my-favorite-songs-012-adam-yauch.jpg' />
                <description>Adam Nathaniel Yauch (August 5, 1964 – May 4, 2012), better known under the stage name MCA, was an American rapper, bass player, filmmaker and a founding member of the hip hop group Beastie Boys. Yauch co-founded the Beastie Boys with Mike &#39;Mike D&#39; Diamond and Adam &#39;Ad-Rock&#39; Horovitz in 1979. The band started off as a hardcore punk group, but soon began experimenting with hip-hop. The band broke huge with their first proper album, Licensed to Ill, in 1986; it was the biggest-selling rap album of the decade and the first to reach Number One on the Billboard chart. Further albums Paul’s Boutique, Check Your Head and Ill Communication cemented the Beasties as a true superstar act. Yauch also directed many of the Beastie Boys’ music videos under the pseudonym Nathaniel Hornblower. In 2002, he founded Oscilloscope Laboratories, an independent film production and distribution company based in New York City. As a Buddhist, he was involved in the Tibetan independence movement and organized the Tibetan Freedom Concert. He died in 2012 from parotid cancer.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Bad Brains, Stiff Little Fingers, Buzzcocks, Generation X, Public Image Ltd., Toots &amp; The Maytals, Linton Kwesi Johnson, Bob Marley &amp; The Wailers, Spoonie Gee, Run–D.M.C., Bob Dylan, Public Enemy, Jimi Hendrix, Jackson Browne, Back Door, The Beatles, Elis Regina, Antônio Carlos Jobim, Kanye West, Mos Def, Freeway, The Boys Choir Of Harlem, Phoenix, The Slits, Killing Joke, New Age Steppers, Young Marble Giants, Minor Threat, Cockney Rejects, Dr. Jeckyll &amp; Mr. Hyde, Grandmaster Flash &amp; The Furious Five, Jocelyn Brown, Frederick M.C. Count Linton, Malcolm McLaren, The Crusaders, Larry Carlton, Beanie Sigel, The Strokes, Arctic Monkeys</description>
                <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 011 by Thurston Moore - Favorite Songs Of All Time</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#011</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-011-thurston-moore</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-011-thurston-moore/all-my-favorite-songs-011-thurston-moore.mp3" length="226106281" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-011-thurston-moore/all-my-favorite-songs-011-thurston-moore.jpg' />
                <description>Thurston Joseph Moore (born July 25, 1958) is an American musician best known as a member of Sonic Youth. He has also participated in many solo and group collaborations outside Sonic Youth, as well as running the Ecstatic Peace! record label. Thurston Moore&#39;s work with Sonic Youth rearranged the parameters of indie rock to an almost incalculable degree, merging experimental art rock tendencies with unconventional guitar tunings for a sound that would influence generations to come. Moore&#39;s abstract poetic lyrics and perpetually mysterious aura were core ingredients of Sonic Youth&#39;s 30-plus-year run, but also bled into countless side projects and less-frequent solo albums like 1994&#39;s sprawling and loose Psychic Hearts. After the group&#39;s breakup in 2011, Moore continued with his ambitions, ranging from projects like his band Chelsea Light Moving to noisy collaborations with Merzbow and John Zorn to solo albums like 2020&#39;s By the Fire that continued exploring the kind of moody, twisting art rock he&#39;d become an icon of with Sonic Youth. Moore was ranked 34th in Rolling Stone&#39;s 2004 edition of the &#39;100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time.&#39; In May 2012, Spin published a staff-selected list of the top 100 rock guitarists, and ranked Moore and his Sonic Youth bandmate Lee Ranaldo together at number 1.   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Tapper Zukie, Patti Smith, Teenage Jesus &amp; The Jerks, MARS, Public Image Ltd., The Slits, The Raincoats, Captain Beefheart &amp; His Magic Band, Alice Cooper, T. Rex, Archie Shepp, Billie Holiday, Teddy Wilson, Nirvana, Mudhoney, Dinosaur Jr., Jackson C. Frank, Bush Tetras, Germs, Boredoms, Lou Reed, The Beach Boys, David Bowie, Sparks, Siouxsie and the Banshees, The Damned, The Mentally Ill, Minor Threat, Black Flag, The Untouchables, Iron Cross, The Faith, Void, Negative Approach, Youth Brigade, S.O.A., Anne Briggs, The Fugs, Jimi Hendrix</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 010 by Mike Patton - Playlist for Henry Rollins</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#010</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-010-mike-patton</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-010-mike-patton/all-my-favorite-songs-010-mike-patton.mp3" length="116232555" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-010-mike-patton/all-my-favorite-songs-010-mike-patton.jpg' />
                <description>Michael Allan Patton (born January 27, 1968) is an American singer, producer, film composer and voice actor, best known as the lead vocalist of the alternative metal band Faith No More. Noted for his vocal proficiency, diverse singing techniques, wide range of projects, style-transcending influences, eccentric public image and contempt for the music industry, Patton has earned critical praise and influenced many contemporary singers. One of the most versatile, innately talented, and idiosyncratic singers in rock music, Mike Patton is also one of the genre&#39;s most valuable players, since he has divided his time between a host of diverse projects including Faith No More, Mr. Bungle, Fantômas, Tomahawk, Peeping Tom, Nevermen, Dead Cross, and an experimental solo career. In addition to his band and solo work, Patton is a gifted actor and producer who has collaborated with a wide array of artists, including John Zorn, Sepultura, Melvins, Melt Banana, and Kool Keith.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Bad Brains, Don Black, John Barry, Tom Jones, Young Fathers, Quincy Jones, Don Elliott, Terveet Kädet, Dead Cross, Jacques Brel, Tom Dissevelt, White Noise, Charlie Parr, Messer Chups, João Gilberto, Funkadelic, Die Kreuzen, Adriano Celentano, Conlon Nancarrow, Bösendorfer Grand Piano, Dion Mcgregor, Basil Kirchin, Chet Baker, Nino Rota, Sun Ra, The Cosmic Rays</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 009 by Slipknot - Halloween Playlist</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#009</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-009-slipknot</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-009-slipknot/all-my-favorite-songs-009-slipknot.mp3" length="221642630" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-009-slipknot/all-my-favorite-songs-009-slipknot.jpg' />
                <description>Slipknot is an American heavy metal band formed in Des Moines, Iowa, in 1995 by percussionist Shawn Crahan, drummer Joey Jordison and bassist Paul Gray. After several lineup changes in its early years, the band settled on nine members for more than a decade: Crahan, Jordison, Gray, Craig Jones, Mick Thomson, Corey Taylor, Sid Wilson, Chris Fehn, and Jim Root. Gray died on May 24, 2010, and was replaced during 2011–2014 by guitarist Donnie Steele. Slipknot&#39;s mix of grinding, post-Korn alternative metal, Marilyn Manson-esque neo-shock rock, and rap-metal helped make them one of the most popular bands in the nu-metal explosion of the late 1990s and early 2000s. But even more helpful was their theatrical, attention-grabbing image: the band always performed in identical industrial jump suits and homemade Halloween masks, and added to their mysterious anonymity by adopting the numbers zero through eight as stage aliases. Add to that a lyrical preoccupation with darkness and nihilism, and an affectionately insulting name for their fans (&#39;Maggots&#39;), and Slipknot&#39;s blueprint for nu-metal success was set.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Slipknot, Talking Heads, S.O.D. Stormtroopers of Death, Dangerous Toys, Iron Maiden, Ho99o9, Refused, Public Enemy, Marilyn Manson, White Zombie, Slayer, Venom, Megadeth, Ice Cube, Dr. Dre, Misfits, Glenn Danzig, Black Sabbath, Judas Priest, Testament, Alice Cooper, Behemoth, Neurosis, Mötley Crüe, Concrete Blonde, W.A.S.P.</description>
                <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 008 by Kurt Vile - Nepotismic Reticulum Top Faves Studio Mixtape</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#008</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-008-kurt-vile</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-008-kurt-vile/all-my-favorite-songs-008-kurt-vile.mp3" length="303395352" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-008-kurt-vile/all-my-favorite-songs-008-kurt-vile.jpg' />
                <description>Kurt Samuel Vile (born January 3, 1980) is an American singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, and record producer. He is known for his solo work and as the former lead guitarist of rock band The War on Drugs. Both in the studio and during live performances, Vile is accompanied by his backing band, The Violators, which currently includes Jesse Trbovich (bass, guitar, saxophone), Rob Laakso (guitar, bass) and Kyle Spence (drums). His laid-back and drifting indie rock takes notes from masters like Neil Young, Sonic Youth, and Dinosaur Jr., exploring inventive guitar tones on meditative and often self-reflective songs.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Stephen Malkmus &amp; The Jicks, Courtney Barnett, DRINKS, Cass McCombs, John Prine, Nathan Bowles, Grouper, Yo La Tengo, Jessica Pratt, Steve Gunn, Kurt Vile, Steely Dan, The Go-Betweens, Nick Cave &amp; The Bad Seeds, Suicide, The Move, Captain Beefheart, Miles Davis, The Sadies, The Pogues, The Rolling Stones, Rusty Kershaw, Doug Kershaw, Willie Dunn, Aphrodite&#39;s Child, Lou Reed, Prince, Depeche Mode, David Bowie, Big Star, Flamin&#39; Groovies, The Byrds, Tim Buckley, Randy Newman, David Byrne, Gary Numan  Tubeway Army</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 007 by SebastiAn - Picks</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#007</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-007-sebastian</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-007-sebastian/all-my-favorite-songs-007-sebastian.mp3" length="277264660" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-007-sebastian/all-my-favorite-songs-007-sebastian.jpg' />
                <description>Sébastien Akchoté-Bozović (born 3 February 1981), known mononymously as Sebastian (stylised as SebastiAn), is a French musician, composer, producer, mixer, engineer, vocalist and DJ affiliated with Ed Banger Records. He has worked as a solo electronic musician and as a remixer for bands and singers such as Charlotte Gainsbourg, Daft Punk, Beastie Boys, Bloc Party, and Nero. He has also composed and produced songs for Charlotte Gainsbourg, Katerine, Kavinsky, Frank Ocean, Uffie and Woodkid, and he has composed soundtracks for the films Our Day Will Come, The World Is Yours and Steak (in which he also acted, credited under the name Sebastian Akchoté). Many of his tracks have been used on television and in video games.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; SebastiAn, Syd, Gary Numan, Bakar, Iggy Pop, Bon Iver, Gallant, Jhené Aiko, A. K. Paul, Mica Levi, Jackson And His Computer Band, TOBACCO, Beck, Frank Ocean, The Waitresses, JPEGMAFIA, Mr. Oizo, Phra, Daft Punk, Sparks, Kavinsky, Lightning Bolt, Chassol, Prince, Mother&#39;s Finest, The Beach Boys, Chet Baker, The Marketts, Mark Bell, Errorsmith, Orchestre Lamoureux, DJ Mehdi, Thomas Roussel, Aphex Twin, Billie Holiday, Catherine Deneuve, Kanye West, PARTYNEXTDOOR, Googoosh, Charlotte Gainsbourg, Ennio Morricone, Hrvoje Hitrec, Wings</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 006 by Wu-Tang Clan - Music Mondays</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#006</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-006-wu-tang-clan</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-006-wu-tang-clan/all-my-favorite-songs-006-wu-tang-clan.mp3" length="130190445" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-006-wu-tang-clan/all-my-favorite-songs-006-wu-tang-clan.jpg' />
                <description>Wu-Tang Clan is an American hip hop group formed in Staten Island, New York City, in 1992. Its original members include RZA, GZA, Ol&#39; Dirty Bastard, Method Man, Raekwon, Ghostface Killah, Inspectah Deck, U-God, and Masta Killa. Close affiliate Cappadonna later became an official member. Wu-Tang Clan are regarded as a highly influential group in hip hop, helping to popularize and develop the East Coast hip hop and hardcore hip hop styles.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Method Man, Wu-Tang Clan, RZA, Inspectah Deck, Raekwon, Ghostface Killah, Cappadonna, Mobb Deep, ODB, The Notorious B.I.G., Gang Starr, U-God, GZA, Masta Killa, GZA (Genius), Nas, Onyx, Ice Cube, Warren G, Nate Dogg, The Pharcyde</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 005 by Nick Cave - Hiding Songs</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#005</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-005-nick-cave</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-005-nick-cave/all-my-favorite-songs-005-nick-cave.mp3" length="108547138" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-005-nick-cave/all-my-favorite-songs-005-nick-cave.jpg' />
                <description>Nicholas Edward Cave AO (born 22 September 1957) is an Australian singer, songwriter, author, screenwriter, composer and occasional actor. Known for his baritone voice and for fronting the rock band Nick Cave and the Bad Seeds, Cave&#39;s music is generally characterised by emotional intensity, a wide variety of influences and lyrical obsessions with death, religion, love and violence.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Since the late &#39;70s, Nick Cave has proved to be one of the most enduring talents to emerge from the post-punk era. In addition to being a remarkably consistent recording artist, his songs have been covered by everyone from Josh Groban, PJ Harvey, and Johnny Cash to Arctic Monkeys, Metallica, and Chelsea Wolfe, to name a few.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Leonard Cohen, Karen Dalton, Neil Young, John Lee Hooker, Van Morrison, Bob Dylan, Nina Simone, Big Star, Brian Eno, Bill Callahan, The Gun Club</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 004 by Viagra Boys - Shrimptech Enterprises Vol.1</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#004</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-004-viagra-boys</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-004-viagra-boys/all-my-favorite-songs-004-viagra-boys.mp3" length="305630792" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-004-viagra-boys/all-my-favorite-songs-004-viagra-boys.jpg' />
                <description>Viagra Boys are a Swedish post-punk band from Stockholm. The band was formed in 2015, with several members coming from the bands Les Big Byrd, Pig Eyes, Nine, Nitad and Neu-Ronz. In 2018, they released their first album, Street Worms. Nils Hansson, a journalist at the newspaper Dagens Nyheter described the band favorably, praising their musical style, as well as their use of black humor and satire, and rated the album a five out of five. In 2019, the band won the Independent Music Companies Association (IMPALA) Album of the Year Award for Street Worms. The band&#39;s second album, Welfare Jazz, was released in January 2021.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Tubeway Army, The Jesus and Mary Chain, Chain and The Gang, DEVO, Goran Kajfes Subtropic Arkestra, Goran Kajfes, Roxy Music, Built To Spill, The Stooges, Waylon Jennings, Clap Your Hands Say Yeah, DAF, Broadcast, Container, Run The Jewels, Spacemen 3, Daniel Lanois, Anna Domino, Rocket From The Tombs, Esbjörn Svensson Trio, Missing Persons, Pere Ubu, Christian Scott aTunde Adjuah, Elena Pinderhughes, Tom Tom Club, 13th Floor Elevators, Sleaford Mods, John Coltrane, Art Ensemble Of Chicago, Pixies, Fire! Orchestra, Richard Hell, The Breeders, Daniel Ögren, Sam Rivers, Chris &amp; Cosey, The Soft Boys, Hawkwind, Joni Mitchell</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 003 by Drive Like Jehu - All Tomorrow's Parties 2.0</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#003</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-003-drive-like-jehu</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-003-drive-like-jehu/all-my-favorite-songs-003-drive-like-jehu.mp3" length="141259537" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-003-drive-like-jehu/all-my-favorite-songs-003-drive-like-jehu.jpg' />
                <description>Drive Like Jehu was an American post-hardcore band from San Diego active from 1990 to 1995. It was formed by rhythm guitarist and vocalist Rick Froberg and lead guitarist John Reis, ex-members of Pitchfork, along with bassist Mike Kennedy and drummer Mark Trombino, both from Night Soil Man, after their two bands disbanded in 1990. Drive Like Jehu&#39;s music was characterized by passionate singing, unusual song structure, indirect melodic themes, intricate guitar playing, and calculated use of tension, resulting in a distinctive sound amongst other post-hardcore acts and helped to catalyze the evolution of hardcore punk into emo.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In this episode all songs by bands selected by Drive Like Jehu to play All Tomorrow&#39;s Parties 2.0 April 22-24, 2016.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Hot Snakes, The Blind Shake, Mrs. Magician, Flamin&#39; Groovies, The King Khan &amp; BBQ Show, The Schizophonics, Metz, Mission Of Burma, The Gories, King Khan and the Shrines, The Spits, Rocket From The Crypt, Betunizer, The Monkeywrench, Holly Golightly, Dan Sartain, Martin Rev, Tortoise, The Ex, PyPy, Gary Wilson, Claw Hammer, Wau y Los Arrrghs</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 002 by Dinosaur Jr. - 80's Inspirations</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#002</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-002-dinosaur-jr</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-002-dinosaur-jr/all-my-favorite-songs-002-dinosaur-jr.mp3" length="87131551" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-002-dinosaur-jr/all-my-favorite-songs-002-dinosaur-jr.jpg' />
                <description>Dinosaur Jr. is an American rock band formed in Amherst, Massachusetts, in 1984, originally simply called Dinosaur until legal issues forced a change in name. The band was founded by J Mascis (guitar, vocals, primary songwriter), Lou Barlow (bass, vocals), and Murph (drums). After three albums on independent labels, the band earned a reputation as one of the formative influences on American alternative rock. Mascis&#39;s drawling vocals and distinct guitar sound, hearkening back to 1960s and 1970s classic rock and characterized by extensive use of feedback and distortion, were highly influential in the alternative rock movement of the 1990s.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Wipers, The Dream Syndicate, True West, The Jesus and Mary Chain, The Birthday Party, Throbbing Gristle, Venom, Accept, Saint Vitus, The Eastern Dark, The Neats, Green On Red, Meat Puppets</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

        <item>
                <title>All My Favorite Songs 001 by Weezer - All My Favorite Songs</title>
                <link>http://allmyfavoritesongs.com#001</link>
                <guid>http://archive.org/details/all-my-favorite-songs-001-weezer</guid>
                <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-001-weezer/all-my-favorite-songs-001-weezer.mp3" length="55457251" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <itunes:image href='http://archive.org/download/all-my-favorite-songs-001-weezer/all-my-favorite-songs-001-weezer.jpg' />
                <description>Weezer is an American rock band formed in Los Angeles, California, in 1992. Since 2001, the band has consisted of Rivers Cuomo (lead vocals, lead guitar, keyboards), Patrick Wilson (drums, percussion, backing vocals), Brian Bell (guitar, backing vocals, keyboards), and Scott Shriner (bass, backing vocals, keyboards).  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lineup: &lt;br /&gt; Neil Young, REO Speedwagon, Johnny Cash, Toni Braxton, Yeah Yeah Yeahs, Céline Dion, Sinéad O&#39;Connor</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:34:56 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        

</channel>

</rss>

